{
"responseHeader":{
"zkConnected":true,
"status":0,
"QTime":33,
"params":{
"q":"text:Bruce Dessau",
"indent":"on",
"wt":"json"}},
"response":{"numFound":64846,"start":0,"maxScore":7.893731,"docs":[
{
"id":"sha1:7FTX2XOZJHYUMOHVJMG2BTBXE6YLW6MU/WM4OYCYCMRVPim2Uw5xOfA==",
"source_file":"BL-20130714050048755-00000-4204~opera~8443.warc.gz",
"source_file_offset":718049593,
"url":"http://www.guardian.co.uk/profile/bruceackerman",
"url_type":["normal"],
"record_type":"response",
"resourcename":["bruceackerman"],
"host":"guardian.co.uk",
"domain":"guardian.co.uk",
"public_suffix":"co.uk",
"server":["Apache"],
"content_type_served":"text/html; charset=utf-8",
"content_length":100423,
"hash":["sha1:7FTX2XOZJHYUMOHVJMG2BTBXE6YLW6MU"],
"crawl_date":"2013-07-15T01:19:02Z",
"crawl_year":"2013",
"wayback_date":"20130715011902",
"access_terms":["RRO"],
"content_text_length":6126,
"content_type":["text/html"],
"title":"Bruce Ackerman | The Guardian",
"keywords":["Global"],
"content_encoding":"UTF-8",
"content_ffb":"20202020",
"content_type_droid":"text/html; version=5",
"links_domains":["e-printphoto.co.uk",
"guardian.co.uk",
"guardianbookshop.co.uk",
"newspaperdirect.com"],
"links_public_suffixes":["com",
"co.uk"],
"elements_used":["body",
"sc\"",
"link/@rel=shortcut icon",
"link",
"div",
"img",
"noscript",
"meta",
"title",
"link/@rel=stylesheet",
"style",
"button",
"link/@rel=publisher",
"e.length;b++){c=e[b].substr(0,e[b].indexof(\"=\"));d=e[b].substr(e[b].indexof(\"=\")+1);c=c.replace(",
"h4",
"ol",
"head",
"h1",
"option",
"h3",
"h2",
"ul",
"form",
"select",
"a",
"link/@rel=shorturl",
"script",
"li",
"link/@rel=alternate",
"link/@rel=canonical",
"input",
"strong",
"p",
"scr\"",
"html",
"scr'",
"span"],
"content_type_tika":"text/html; charset=UTF-8",
"content_type_version":"5",
"content_type_full":"text/html; charset=UTF-8; version=5",
"content_type_norm":"html",
"content_language":"en",
"ssdeep_hash_bs_96":"kpujz5m8dWBC9nNWiyQ+0jLAD6ozV6/6GXkzWqDmZ3EnmYHrKRy3utVFtJGows8M",
"ssdeep_hash_bs_192":"kYz5sYcMANp6/6GWmGfL6GgdG41mO",
"ssdeep_hash_ngram_bs_96":"kpujz5m8dWBC9nNWiyQ+0jLAD6ozV6/6GXkzWqDmZ3EnmYHrKRy3utVFtJGows8M",
"ssdeep_hash_ngram_bs_192":"kYz5sYcMANp6/6GWmGfL6GgdG41mO",
"crawl_dates":["2013-07-15T01:19:02Z"],
"crawl_years":["2013"],
"_version_":1569733322707304448,
"type":"Other",
"content":["Turn autoplay off Turn autoplay on Please activate cookies in order to turn autoplay off Jump to content [s] Jump to site navigation [0] Jump to search [4] Terms and conditions [8] Edition: UK US AU Your activity Email subscriptions Account details Linked services Profile Mobile About us About us, Contact us Press office Guardian Print Centre Guardian readers' editor Observer readers' editor Terms of service Privacy policy Advertising guide Digital archive Digital edition Guardian Weekly Buy Guardian and Observer photos Today's paper The Guardian G2 features Comment and debate Editorials, letters and corrections Obituaries Other lives Sport MediaGuardian Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe to the Guardian iPhone app iPad edition Kindle Extra Guardian Weekly Digital edition The Guardian User comments News Sport Comment Culture Business Money Life & style Travel Environment Tech TV Video Dating Offers Jobs Global Bruce Ackerman RSS Profile Bruce Ackerman is Sterling professor of law and political science at Yale, and the author of Before the Next Attack: Preserving Civil Liberties in an Age of Terrorism (2006) and, most recently, The Decline and Fall of the American Republic (2010) Latest How to make a European constitution for the 21st century 3 Oct 2012: Bruce Ackerman and Miguel Maduro: Europe needs a solution to its crisis that will be accepted by its citizens. The South African model may be the answer How to resolve the War Powers impasse 3 Jun 2011: Bruce Ackerman and Oona Hathaway: Dennis Kucinich is wrong about Libya but right about the law: Congress and the president must fix this War Powers Act hiatus Bradley Manning's inhumane treatment 11 Apr 2011: Bruce Ackerman and others: Open letter: The president's own legal training must tell him how the abuse of the alleged WikiLeaks source violates constitutional norms Did Congress approve America's longest war? 27 Jan 2011: Bruce Ackerman and Oona Hathaway: Congress did empower the president in 2001 to pursue al-Qaida in Afghanistan. But a decade later, where's the oversight? Charging Julian Assange could be unconstitutional 10 Dec 2010: Bruce Ackerman and Sara Aronchick Solow: The due process clause rules out prosecuting WikiLeaks' founder – a non-US citizen – for extraterritorial offences Laugh Lines: from Sergeant Bilko to Father Ted 13 May 2010: Bruce Dessau's guide to TV comedy: Forget Steve Martin, it is the spirit of Phil Silvers that is resurrected on Craggy Island Why the Lib Dems do well out of TV debates 29 Apr 2010: Bruce Ackerman and James Fishkin: The leaders' debates have prompted voters to re-examine their old party identities in light of their policy preferences A national endowment for journalism 13 Feb 2009: Bruce Ackerman and Ian Ayres: Efforts to save print newspapers are missing the point. The real question is how to save investigative reporting A legal time bomb in Iraq 12 Dec 2008: Bruce Ackerman and Oona Hathaway: Obama must return US foreign policy to the rule of law - and the mandate for war is about to expire The coming transatlantic crisis 2 Sep 2008: Bruce Ackerman: Russia's resurgence as a world power and America's decline mean that US and European interests are on a collision course What Georgia means for Europe 12 Aug 2008: Bruce Ackerman: Russia's military hostilities in Georgia provides a new impetus for strengthening the European Union Where money is no object 26 Jan 2008: Bruce Ackerman and Ian Ayres: Peter Hain's disgrace will inevitably lead to calls for campaign finance reform. The best solution is for political donations to be made anonymously into blind trusts Checks, please 15 Jan 2008: Bruce Ackerman: US elections 2008: The US political system succeeds, not fails, when it stalls large change until there is a broad consensus to support it Inherit the windfall 11 Oct 2007: Bruce Ackerman and Anne Alstott: Funding baby bonds with the tax on private inheritance is both fair and just. What we owe 'suspected terrorists' 23 Jul 2007: Bruce Ackerman: Compensating detainees who turn out to be innocent is the right thing to do, and would create economic incentives that improve the fight against terrorism. Next 1 2 1-15 of 17 for Bruce Ackerman Today's best video Adam Sandler pounced on by cheetah on safari American actor Adam Sandler introduces footage of himself being pounced on by a cheetah while on holiday in Africa Tour de France video highlights Chris Froome becomes the first British cyclist to win on Mount Ventoux Goal scored from inside own half FC Red Bull Salzburg central defender Martin Hinteregger gives a ball wings Kitten found on London tube train Four-week-old kitten found at Victoria underground station On The Guardian Most viewed Latest Last 24 hours 1.  Comment: Open season on black boys after a verdict like this | Gary Younge 2. World: Obama's secret kill list – the disposition matrix 3. Football: Arsenal to test Liverpool's resolve with new £35m bid for Luis Suárez 4. TV & radio: Glee star Cory Monteith found dead in hotel room 5. TV & radio: Cory Monteith co-stars pay tribute after Glee actor's death More most viewed Last 24 hours 1.  Neighbourhood Watch groups should look after old – health minister 2. AFL: five things we learned this weekend 3. Two men stabbed at music festival featuring Justin Timberlake and Jay-Z 4. Pilot and passenger killed as light aircraft crashes in Leicestershire 5. Alastair Cook, Michael Clarke and James Anderson reflect on the first Ashes Test - video All today's stories This week's bestsellers 1.  Ten Billion by Stephen Emmott £5.59 2.  NHS SOS by Raymond Tallis £6.99 3.  Reason I Jump: One Boy's Voice from the Silence of Autism by Naoki Higashida £10.39 4.  Sweet Tooth by Ian McEwan £4.79 5.  Old Ways by Robert Macfarlane £7.99 Search the Guardian bookshop Search Sponsored feature License/buy our content | Privacy policy | Terms & conditions | Advertising guide | Accessibility | A-Z index | Inside the Guardian blog | About us | Work for us | Join our dating site today © 2013 Guardian News and Media Limited or its affiliated companies. All rights reserved. Close notifications (beta)"]},
{
"id":"sha1:ZANWWEYIHYEBJBPDISMIK2IMNKDB6Z5C/WM4OYCYCMRVPim2Uw5xOfA==",
"source_file":"BL-20130720050046075-00002-4204~opera~8443.warc.gz",
"source_file_offset":429932895,
"url":"http://www.guardian.co.uk/profile/bruceackerman",
"url_type":["normal"],
"record_type":"response",
"resourcename":["bruceackerman"],
"host":"guardian.co.uk",
"domain":"guardian.co.uk",
"public_suffix":"co.uk",
"server":["Apache"],
"content_type_served":"text/html; charset=utf-8",
"content_length":103212,
"hash":["sha1:ZANWWEYIHYEBJBPDISMIK2IMNKDB6Z5C"],
"crawl_date":"2013-07-20T21:48:00Z",
"crawl_year":"2013",
"wayback_date":"20130720214800",
"access_terms":["RRO"],
"content_text_length":6143,
"content_type":["text/html"],
"title":"Bruce Ackerman | The Guardian",
"keywords":["Global"],
"content_encoding":"UTF-8",
"content_ffb":"20202020",
"content_type_droid":"text/html; version=5",
"links_domains":["e-printphoto.co.uk",
"guardian.co.uk",
"guardianbookshop.co.uk",
"newspaperdirect.com"],
"links_public_suffixes":["com",
"co.uk"],
"elements_used":["body",
"sc\"",
"link/@rel=shortcut icon",
"link",
"div",
"img",
"noscript",
"meta",
"title",
"link/@rel=stylesheet",
"style",
"button",
"link/@rel=publisher",
"e.length;b++){c=e[b].substr(0,e[b].indexof(\"=\"));d=e[b].substr(e[b].indexof(\"=\")+1);c=c.replace(",
"h4",
"ol",
"head",
"h1",
"option",
"h3",
"h2",
"ul",
"form",
"select",
"a",
"link/@rel=shorturl",
"script",
"li",
"link/@rel=alternate",
"link/@rel=canonical",
"input",
"strong",
"p",
"scr\"",
"html",
"scr'",
"span"],
"content_type_tika":"text/html; charset=UTF-8",
"content_type_version":"5",
"content_type_full":"text/html; charset=UTF-8; version=5",
"content_type_norm":"html",
"content_language":"en",
"ssdeep_hash_bs_96":"kpujz5mcqWWBC9nNWiyQ+0jLAD6ozV6/6GXkzWqDmZ3EnmYHrAVX3xkW+HyYv/7w",
"ssdeep_hash_bs_192":"kYz5sfYcMANp6/6GWmGfLAVX3JSH69d5",
"ssdeep_hash_ngram_bs_96":"kpujz5mcqWWBC9nNWiyQ+0jLAD6ozV6/6GXkzWqDmZ3EnmYHrAVX3xkW+HyYv/7w",
"ssdeep_hash_ngram_bs_192":"kYz5sfYcMANp6/6GWmGfLAVX3JSH69d5",
"crawl_dates":["2013-07-20T21:48:00Z"],
"crawl_years":["2013"],
"_version_":1569733129228255232,
"type":"Other",
"content":["Turn autoplay off Turn autoplay on Please activate cookies in order to turn autoplay off Jump to content [s] Jump to site navigation [0] Jump to search [4] Terms and conditions [8] Edition: UK US AU Your activity Email subscriptions Account details Linked services Profile Mobile About us About us, Contact us Press office Guardian Print Centre Guardian readers' editor Observer readers' editor Terms of service Privacy policy Advertising guide Digital archive Digital edition Guardian Weekly Buy Guardian and Observer photos Today's paper The Guardian Comment and debate Editorials, letters and corrections Obituaries Other lives Sport Review Travel Family Money Work Weekend The Guide Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe to the Guardian iPhone app iPad edition Kindle Extra Guardian Weekly Digital edition The Guardian User comments News Sport Comment Culture Business Money Life & style Travel Environment Tech TV Video Dating Offers Jobs Global Bruce Ackerman RSS Profile Bruce Ackerman is Sterling professor of law and political science at Yale, and the author of Before the Next Attack: Preserving Civil Liberties in an Age of Terrorism (2006) and, most recently, The Decline and Fall of the American Republic (2010) Latest How to make a European constitution for the 21st century 3 Oct 2012: Bruce Ackerman and Miguel Maduro: Europe needs a solution to its crisis that will be accepted by its citizens. The South African model may be the answer How to resolve the War Powers impasse 3 Jun 2011: Bruce Ackerman and Oona Hathaway: Dennis Kucinich is wrong about Libya but right about the law: Congress and the president must fix this War Powers Act hiatus Bradley Manning's inhumane treatment 11 Apr 2011: Bruce Ackerman and others: Open letter: The president's own legal training must tell him how the abuse of the alleged WikiLeaks source violates constitutional norms Did Congress approve America's longest war? 27 Jan 2011: Bruce Ackerman and Oona Hathaway: Congress did empower the president in 2001 to pursue al-Qaida in Afghanistan. But a decade later, where's the oversight? Charging Julian Assange could be unconstitutional 10 Dec 2010: Bruce Ackerman and Sara Aronchick Solow: The due process clause rules out prosecuting WikiLeaks' founder – a non-US citizen – for extraterritorial offences Laugh Lines: from Sergeant Bilko to Father Ted 13 May 2010: Bruce Dessau's guide to TV comedy: Forget Steve Martin, it is the spirit of Phil Silvers that is resurrected on Craggy Island Why the Lib Dems do well out of TV debates 29 Apr 2010: Bruce Ackerman and James Fishkin: The leaders' debates have prompted voters to re-examine their old party identities in light of their policy preferences A national endowment for journalism 13 Feb 2009: Bruce Ackerman and Ian Ayres: Efforts to save print newspapers are missing the point. The real question is how to save investigative reporting A legal time bomb in Iraq 12 Dec 2008: Bruce Ackerman and Oona Hathaway: Obama must return US foreign policy to the rule of law - and the mandate for war is about to expire The coming transatlantic crisis 2 Sep 2008: Bruce Ackerman: Russia's resurgence as a world power and America's decline mean that US and European interests are on a collision course What Georgia means for Europe 12 Aug 2008: Bruce Ackerman: Russia's military hostilities in Georgia provides a new impetus for strengthening the European Union Where money is no object 26 Jan 2008: Bruce Ackerman and Ian Ayres: Peter Hain's disgrace will inevitably lead to calls for campaign finance reform. The best solution is for political donations to be made anonymously into blind trusts Checks, please 15 Jan 2008: Bruce Ackerman: US elections 2008: The US political system succeeds, not fails, when it stalls large change until there is a broad consensus to support it Inherit the windfall 11 Oct 2007: Bruce Ackerman and Anne Alstott: Funding baby bonds with the tax on private inheritance is both fair and just. What we owe 'suspected terrorists' 23 Jul 2007: Bruce Ackerman: Compensating detainees who turn out to be innocent is the right thing to do, and would create economic incentives that improve the fight against terrorism. Next 1 2 1-15 of 17 for Bruce Ackerman Today's best video The Guardian Film Show Our critics review The World's End (starring Simon Pegg, above), Breathe In, Wadjda and The Frozen Ground Goalkeeper plays 1956 FA Cup Final with broken neck Heroism from Manchester City's Bert Trautmann, who has died aged 89 How to catch a crocodile Queensland's ranger-in-charge explains how he removes crocodiles from waterways Is it a bird? Is it a plane? No, it's the Birdman of Bognor Gliding contest takes place in West Sussex On The Guardian Most viewed Latest Last 24 hours 1.  Film: Nicolas Cage: 'People think I'm not in on the joke' 2. World: 'Justice for Trayvon Martin' rallies taking place in 100 US cities- live updates 3. Culture: Comedian Mel Smith dies 4. Sport: Ashes 2013: Joe Root ton gives England total control against Australia 5. Fashion: Sali Hughes's 25 top fixes to keep you looking young – without surgery More most viewed Last 24 hours 1.  The Bouncer: Shane Watson has a bellyful of England's middle order 2. NHS chief says sorry to Andy Burnham for Tory 'smear' campaign 3. Academy chain under fire following revelation of payments made to bosses 4. Top of the Lake recap: season one, episode two – Searchers Search 5. Lee Westwood: 'I know what it takes to win at the Open, I feel confident' All today's stories This week's bestsellers 1.  Sweet Tooth by Ian McEwan £4.79 2.  Reason I Jump: One Boy's Voice from the Silence of Autism by Naoki Higashida £10.39 3.  Ten Billion by Stephen Emmott £5.59 4.  NHS SOS by Raymond Tallis £6.99 5.  Racing Hard by William Fotheringham £8.99 Search the Guardian bookshop Search Sponsored feature License/buy our content | Privacy policy | Terms & conditions | Advertising guide | Accessibility | A-Z index | Inside the Guardian blog | About us | Work for us | Join our dating site today © 2013 Guardian News and Media Limited or its affiliated companies. All rights reserved. Close notifications (beta)"]},
{
"id":"sha1:PQYX2TBVXJWXF7U2WZ74JWCHBAIDSA3Y/WM4OYCYCMRVPim2Uw5xOfA==",
"source_file":"BL-20130715050048799-00000-4204~opera~8443.warc.gz",
"source_file_offset":620585162,
"url":"http://www.guardian.co.uk/profile/bruceackerman",
"url_type":["normal"],
"record_type":"response",
"resourcename":["bruceackerman"],
"host":"guardian.co.uk",
"domain":"guardian.co.uk",
"public_suffix":"co.uk",
"server":["Apache"],
"content_type_served":"text/html; charset=utf-8",
"content_length":96054,
"hash":["sha1:PQYX2TBVXJWXF7U2WZ74JWCHBAIDSA3Y"],
"crawl_date":"2013-07-15T21:10:42Z",
"crawl_year":"2013",
"wayback_date":"20130715211042",
"access_terms":["RRO"],
"content_text_length":5579,
"content_type":["text/html"],
"title":"Bruce Ackerman | The Guardian",
"keywords":["Global"],
"content_encoding":"UTF-8",
"content_ffb":"20202020",
"content_type_droid":"text/html; version=5",
"links_domains":["guardian.co.uk",
"guardiannews.com",
"guardianbookshop.co.uk",
"amazon.com",
"newspaperdirect.com"],
"links_public_suffixes":["com",
"co.uk"],
"elements_used":["body",
"sc\"",
"link/@rel=shortcut icon",
"link",
"div",
"img",
"noscript",
"meta",
"title",
"link/@rel=stylesheet",
"style",
"button",
"link/@rel=publisher",
"e.length;b++){c=e[b].substr(0,e[b].indexof(\"=\"));d=e[b].substr(e[b].indexof(\"=\")+1);c=c.replace(",
"h4",
"ol",
"head",
"h1",
"option",
"h3",
"h2",
"ul",
"form",
"select",
"a",
"link/@rel=shorturl",
"script",
"li",
"link/@rel=alternate",
"link/@rel=canonical",
"input",
"strong",
"p",
"scr\"",
"html",
"scr'",
"span"],
"content_type_tika":"text/html; charset=UTF-8",
"content_type_version":"5",
"content_type_full":"text/html; charset=UTF-8; version=5",
"content_type_norm":"html",
"content_language":"en",
"ssdeep_hash_bs_96":"kpujUBC9nNWiyQ+0jLAD6ozV6/6GXkzWqDmZ3EnmYHrmzV18bLMqU1QCzzPPWgc",
"ssdeep_hash_bs_192":"k7YcMANp6/6GWmGfL0VBf1QCPPPWgc",
"ssdeep_hash_ngram_bs_96":"kpujUBC9nNWiyQ+0jLAD6ozV6/6GXkzWqDmZ3EnmYHrmzV18bLMqU1QCzzPPWgc",
"ssdeep_hash_ngram_bs_192":"k7YcMANp6/6GWmGfL0VBf1QCPPPWgc",
"crawl_dates":["2013-07-15T21:10:42Z"],
"crawl_years":["2013"],
"_version_":1569733162921099266,
"type":"Other",
"content":["Turn autoplay off Turn autoplay on Please activate cookies in order to turn autoplay off Jump to content [s] Jump to site navigation [0] Jump to search [4] Terms and conditions [8] Edition: US UK AU Your activity Email subscriptions Account details Linked services Profile Mobile About us About us Contact us Press office Terms of service Privacy policy Subscribe Guardian iPhone iPad edition Kindle Guardian Weekly Digital edition The Guardian User comments News US World Sports Comment Culture Business Money Environment Science Travel Tech Media Life & style Data Global Bruce Ackerman RSS Profile Bruce Ackerman is Sterling professor of law and political science at Yale, and the author of Before the Next Attack: Preserving Civil Liberties in an Age of Terrorism (2006) and, most recently, The Decline and Fall of the American Republic (2010) Latest How to make a European constitution for the 21st century 3 Oct 2012: Bruce Ackerman and Miguel Maduro: Europe needs a solution to its crisis that will be accepted by its citizens. The South African model may be the answer How to resolve the War Powers impasse 3 Jun 2011: Bruce Ackerman and Oona Hathaway: Dennis Kucinich is wrong about Libya but right about the law: Congress and the president must fix this War Powers Act hiatus Bradley Manning's inhumane treatment 11 Apr 2011: Bruce Ackerman and others: Open letter: The president's own legal training must tell him how the abuse of the alleged WikiLeaks source violates constitutional norms Did Congress approve America's longest war? 27 Jan 2011: Bruce Ackerman and Oona Hathaway: Congress did empower the president in 2001 to pursue al-Qaida in Afghanistan. But a decade later, where's the oversight? Charging Julian Assange could be unconstitutional 10 Dec 2010: Bruce Ackerman and Sara Aronchick Solow: The due process clause rules out prosecuting WikiLeaks' founder – a non-US citizen – for extraterritorial offences Laugh Lines: from Sergeant Bilko to Father Ted 13 May 2010: Bruce Dessau's guide to TV comedy: Forget Steve Martin, it is the spirit of Phil Silvers that is resurrected on Craggy Island Why the Lib Dems do well out of TV debates 29 Apr 2010: Bruce Ackerman and James Fishkin: The leaders' debates have prompted voters to re-examine their old party identities in light of their policy preferences A national endowment for journalism 13 Feb 2009: Bruce Ackerman and Ian Ayres: Efforts to save print newspapers are missing the point. The real question is how to save investigative reporting A legal time bomb in Iraq 12 Dec 2008: Bruce Ackerman and Oona Hathaway: Obama must return US foreign policy to the rule of law - and the mandate for war is about to expire The coming transatlantic crisis 2 Sep 2008: Bruce Ackerman: Russia's resurgence as a world power and America's decline mean that US and European interests are on a collision course What Georgia means for Europe 12 Aug 2008: Bruce Ackerman: Russia's military hostilities in Georgia provides a new impetus for strengthening the European Union Where money is no object 26 Jan 2008: Bruce Ackerman and Ian Ayres: Peter Hain's disgrace will inevitably lead to calls for campaign finance reform. The best solution is for political donations to be made anonymously into blind trusts Checks, please 15 Jan 2008: Bruce Ackerman: US elections 2008: The US political system succeeds, not fails, when it stalls large change until there is a broad consensus to support it Inherit the windfall 11 Oct 2007: Bruce Ackerman and Anne Alstott: Funding baby bonds with the tax on private inheritance is both fair and just. What we owe 'suspected terrorists' 23 Jul 2007: Bruce Ackerman: Compensating detainees who turn out to be innocent is the right thing to do, and would create economic incentives that improve the fight against terrorism. Next 1 2 1-15 of 17 for Bruce Ackerman Today's best video Tour de France 2013 highlights: Chris Froome wins stage 15 Chris Froome becomes the first British cyclist to win on Mount Ventoux Protests after George Zimmerman acquitted in Trayvon Martin case Protesters gather outside Florida courthouse How to pan-fry a steak Find out the best way to cook a succulent steak with our step-by-step video guide Is the internet bringing out the best in us? Susan Greenfield and David Babb lock horns in a five-minute debate On The Guardian Most viewed Latest Last 24 hours 1.  World: US under pressure to bring federal charges against George Zimmerman 2. Politics: Tories draw neck and neck with Labour as Ukip support falls 3. Sport: Sky's Dave Brailsford offers Wada access to data to quell doping talk 4. Life & style: How to have hot sex 5. Education: Do you know your onions? More most viewed Last 24 hours 1.  Georgia inmate Warren Hill granted last-minute stay of execution 2. The best news photographs of the day 3. Ireland's leading gay rights campaigner causes outrage over 'sexist' insult 4. Richard Hannon decides to appeal over Sky Lantern's contentious defeat 5. Transfer talk in brief All today's stories This week's bestsellers 1.  Ten Billion by Stephen Emmott £5.59 2.  Reason I Jump: One Boy's Voice from the Silence of Autism by Naoki Higashida £10.39 3.  NHS SOS by Raymond Tallis £6.99 4.  Sweet Tooth by Ian McEwan £4.79 5.  Old Ways by Robert Macfarlane £7.99 Search the Guardian bookshop Search Sponsored feature License/buy our content | Privacy policy | Terms of service | US Advertising | A - Z index | About guardiannews.com © 2013 Guardian News and Media Limited or its affiliated companies. All rights reserved. Close notifications (beta) ;"]},
{
"id":"sha1:NSJWNT7C75W7LT2KSANKUOQ436LIKDKM/WM4OYCYCMRVPim2Uw5xOfA==",
"source_file":"BL-20130713050058355-00000-4204~opera~8443.warc.gz",
"source_file_offset":384987581,
"url":"http://www.guardian.co.uk/profile/bruceackerman",
"url_type":["normal"],
"record_type":"response",
"resourcename":["bruceackerman"],
"host":"guardian.co.uk",
"domain":"guardian.co.uk",
"public_suffix":"co.uk",
"server":["Apache"],
"content_type_served":"text/html; charset=utf-8",
"content_length":101761,
"hash":["sha1:NSJWNT7C75W7LT2KSANKUOQ436LIKDKM"],
"crawl_date":"2013-07-13T22:13:34Z",
"crawl_year":"2013",
"wayback_date":"20130713221334",
"access_terms":["RRO"],
"content_text_length":6095,
"content_type":["text/html"],
"title":"Bruce Ackerman | The Guardian",
"keywords":["Global"],
"content_encoding":"UTF-8",
"content_ffb":"20202020",
"content_type_droid":"text/html; version=5",
"links_domains":["e-printphoto.co.uk",
"guardian.co.uk",
"guardianbookshop.co.uk",
"newspaperdirect.com"],
"links_public_suffixes":["com",
"co.uk"],
"elements_used":["body",
"sc\"",
"link/@rel=shortcut icon",
"link",
"div",
"img",
"noscript",
"meta",
"title",
"link/@rel=stylesheet",
"style",
"button",
"link/@rel=publisher",
"e.length;b++){c=e[b].substr(0,e[b].indexof(\"=\"));d=e[b].substr(e[b].indexof(\"=\")+1);c=c.replace(",
"h4",
"ol",
"head",
"h1",
"option",
"h3",
"h2",
"ul",
"form",
"select",
"a",
"link/@rel=shorturl",
"script",
"li",
"link/@rel=alternate",
"link/@rel=canonical",
"input",
"strong",
"p",
"scr\"",
"html",
"scr'",
"span"],
"content_type_tika":"text/html; charset=UTF-8",
"content_type_version":"5",
"content_type_full":"text/html; charset=UTF-8; version=5",
"content_type_norm":"html",
"content_language":"en",
"ssdeep_hash_bs_96":"kpujz5mcqWWBC9nNWiyQ+0jLAD6ozV6/6GXkzWqDmZ3EnmYHryee+iy3uueb19SS",
"ssdeep_hash_bs_192":"kYz5sfYcMANp6/6GWmGfLye1iGX+19l3",
"ssdeep_hash_ngram_bs_96":"kpujz5mcqWWBC9nNWiyQ+0jLAD6ozV6/6GXkzWqDmZ3EnmYHryee+iy3uueb19SS",
"ssdeep_hash_ngram_bs_192":"kYz5sfYcMANp6/6GWmGfLye1iGX+19l3",
"crawl_dates":["2013-07-13T22:13:34Z"],
"crawl_years":["2013"],
"_version_":1569733292994854912,
"type":"Other",
"content":["Turn autoplay off Turn autoplay on Please activate cookies in order to turn autoplay off Jump to content [s] Jump to site navigation [0] Jump to search [4] Terms and conditions [8] Edition: UK US AU Your activity Email subscriptions Account details Linked services Profile Mobile About us About us, Contact us Press office Guardian Print Centre Guardian readers' editor Observer readers' editor Terms of service Privacy policy Advertising guide Digital archive Digital edition Guardian Weekly Buy Guardian and Observer photos Today's paper The Guardian Comment and debate Editorials, letters and corrections Obituaries Other lives Sport Review Travel Family Money Work Weekend The Guide Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe to the Guardian iPhone app iPad edition Kindle Extra Guardian Weekly Digital edition The Guardian User comments News Sport Comment Culture Business Money Life & style Travel Environment Tech TV Video Dating Offers Jobs Global Bruce Ackerman RSS Profile Bruce Ackerman is Sterling professor of law and political science at Yale, and the author of Before the Next Attack: Preserving Civil Liberties in an Age of Terrorism (2006) and, most recently, The Decline and Fall of the American Republic (2010) Latest How to make a European constitution for the 21st century 3 Oct 2012: Bruce Ackerman and Miguel Maduro: Europe needs a solution to its crisis that will be accepted by its citizens. The South African model may be the answer How to resolve the War Powers impasse 3 Jun 2011: Bruce Ackerman and Oona Hathaway: Dennis Kucinich is wrong about Libya but right about the law: Congress and the president must fix this War Powers Act hiatus Bradley Manning's inhumane treatment 11 Apr 2011: Bruce Ackerman and others: Open letter: The president's own legal training must tell him how the abuse of the alleged WikiLeaks source violates constitutional norms Did Congress approve America's longest war? 27 Jan 2011: Bruce Ackerman and Oona Hathaway: Congress did empower the president in 2001 to pursue al-Qaida in Afghanistan. But a decade later, where's the oversight? Charging Julian Assange could be unconstitutional 10 Dec 2010: Bruce Ackerman and Sara Aronchick Solow: The due process clause rules out prosecuting WikiLeaks' founder – a non-US citizen – for extraterritorial offences Laugh Lines: from Sergeant Bilko to Father Ted 13 May 2010: Bruce Dessau's guide to TV comedy: Forget Steve Martin, it is the spirit of Phil Silvers that is resurrected on Craggy Island Why the Lib Dems do well out of TV debates 29 Apr 2010: Bruce Ackerman and James Fishkin: The leaders' debates have prompted voters to re-examine their old party identities in light of their policy preferences A national endowment for journalism 13 Feb 2009: Bruce Ackerman and Ian Ayres: Efforts to save print newspapers are missing the point. The real question is how to save investigative reporting A legal time bomb in Iraq 12 Dec 2008: Bruce Ackerman and Oona Hathaway: Obama must return US foreign policy to the rule of law - and the mandate for war is about to expire The coming transatlantic crisis 2 Sep 2008: Bruce Ackerman: Russia's resurgence as a world power and America's decline mean that US and European interests are on a collision course What Georgia means for Europe 12 Aug 2008: Bruce Ackerman: Russia's military hostilities in Georgia provides a new impetus for strengthening the European Union Where money is no object 26 Jan 2008: Bruce Ackerman and Ian Ayres: Peter Hain's disgrace will inevitably lead to calls for campaign finance reform. The best solution is for political donations to be made anonymously into blind trusts Checks, please 15 Jan 2008: Bruce Ackerman: US elections 2008: The US political system succeeds, not fails, when it stalls large change until there is a broad consensus to support it Inherit the windfall 11 Oct 2007: Bruce Ackerman and Anne Alstott: Funding baby bonds with the tax on private inheritance is both fair and just. What we owe 'suspected terrorists' 23 Jul 2007: Bruce Ackerman: Compensating detainees who turn out to be innocent is the right thing to do, and would create economic incentives that improve the fight against terrorism. Next 1 2 1-15 of 17 for Bruce Ackerman Today's best video Adam Sandler pounced on by cheetah on safari American actor Adam Sandler introduces footage of himself being pounced on by a cheetah while on holiday in Africa The Guardian Film Show Monsters University, Pacific Rim, Blancanieves and We Steal Secrets reviewed Goal scored from inside own half FC Red Bull Salzburg central defender Martin Hinteregger gives a ball wings Kitten found on London tube train Four-week-old kitten found at Victoria underground station On The Guardian Most viewed Latest Last 24 hours 1.  Culture: The 10 best sea pictures 2. Sport: Australia's Ashton Agar stands in way of a glorious England victory 3. Politics: David Cameron told to sack strategy chief over link to tobacco giants 4. Football: David Moyes' Manchester United reign starts with 1-0 defeat in Bangkok 5. Film: Adam Sandler pounced on by cheetah on safari - video More most viewed Last 24 hours 1.  Labour boost lead over Tories to 11%, says poll 2. Alex Scott puts England success before milestone of her 100th cap 3. Arsenal have talent to end their trophy drought, says Per Mertesacker 4. The Americans recap: season one, episode seven 5. Top of the Lake recap: season one, episode one – Paradise Sold All today's stories This week's bestsellers 1.  NHS SOS by Raymond Tallis £6.74 2.  Ten Billion by Stephen Emmott £5.24 3.  Reason I Jump: One Boy's Voice from the Silence of Autism by Naoki Higashida £9.74 4.  Undercover by Paul Lewis & Rob Evans £8.49 5.  Old Ways by Robert Macfarlane £7.49 Search the Guardian bookshop Search Sponsored feature License/buy our content | Privacy policy | Terms & conditions | Advertising guide | Accessibility | A-Z index | Inside the Guardian blog | About us | Work for us | Join our dating site today © 2013 Guardian News and Media Limited or its affiliated companies. All rights reserved. Close notifications (beta)"]},
{
"id":"sha1:H72TMN2V3OQI5Q5DZFFZCPE5ASN6M24F/72iewzvijAD1jMD4l6vy8A==",
"source_file":"BL-20130724135802442-00001-23954~opera~8443.warc.gz",
"source_file_offset":36286028,
"url":"http://www.walesonline.co.uk/whats-on/music/",
"url_type":["normal"],
"record_type":"response",
"host":"walesonline.co.uk",
"domain":"walesonline.co.uk",
"public_suffix":"co.uk",
"content_type_served":"text/html;charset=UTF-8",
"server":["Apache-Coyote/1.1"],
"content_length":125888,
"hash":["sha1:H72TMN2V3OQI5Q5DZFFZCPE5ASN6M24F"],
"crawl_date":"2013-07-24T14:56:51Z",
"crawl_year":"2013",
"wayback_date":"20130724145651",
"wct_subjects":["Arts & Humanities",
"Society & Culture",
"News and Contemporary Events",
"Sports and Recreation",
"Communities"],
"collection":["100 Best Sites"],
"collections":["100 Best Sites",
"News Sites",
"News Sites|Web only news sites"],
"access_terms":["RRO"],
"content_text_length":14582,
"content_type":["text/html"],
"title":"Music: Find the latest music events across Wales from WalesOnline",
"content_encoding":"UTF-8",
"content_ffb":"3c21646f",
"content_type_droid":"text/html; version=5",
"links_domains":["bookanad.com",
"newmarket.travel",
"facebook.com",
"pcc.org.uk",
"muzu.tv",
"icnetwork.co.uk",
"mediawales.co.uk",
"twitter.com",
"jobswales.co.uk",
"walesonline.co.uk"],
"links_public_suffixes":["org.uk",
"com",
"tv",
"co.uk",
"travel"],
"elements_used":["dt",
"body",
"link",
"div",
"img",
"noscript",
"figcaption",
"br",
"meta",
"dd",
"time",
"title",
"figure",
"link/@rel=stylesheet",
"style",
"link/@rel=pingback",
"h5",
"dl",
"h4",
"h1",
"head",
"h3",
"h2",
"ul",
"form",
"a",
"blockquote",
"label",
"script",
"header",
"footer",
"scr'+'ipt",
"li",
"link/@rel=alternate",
"input",
"iframe",
"p",
"nav",
"html",
"link/@rel=dns-prefetch",
"span"],
"content_type_tika":"text/html; charset=UTF-8",
"content_type_version":"5",
"content_type_full":"text/html; charset=UTF-8; version=5",
"content_type_norm":"html",
"content_language":"en",
"ssdeep_hash_bs_384":"rZP18tgVw8Tl/bETOaycUonm7kB4F9RoQhcxRQpmzz+z",
"ssdeep_hash_bs_768":"rZP18MwAFbETxyFK0kPQY2Qz+z",
"ssdeep_hash_ngram_bs_384":"rZP18tgVw8Tl/bETOaycUonm7kB4F9RoQhcxRQpmzz+z",
"ssdeep_hash_ngram_bs_768":"rZP18MwAFbETxyFK0kPQY2Qz+z",
"crawl_dates":["2013-07-24T14:56:51Z"],
"crawl_years":["2013"],
"_version_":1569733254097928192,
"type":"Other",
"content":["Jobs Motors Property Business Directory Family Notices Travel Dating Book an Ad BuySell Subscriptions Contact Us How we use Cookies Your Account Edit Profile Logout Wales Online 5 day forecast » Home News Latest News Wales News Business UK News World News Crime Politics Health Education Farming News Opinion Trending Today Kate Middleton Prince Charles, Prince of Wales Geraint Thomas Carwyn Jones Heather Joyce Popular this week Letters to the Editor Royal Welsh Show Kate Middleton Top News Live: Wales breaking news, Wednesday 24 July, 2013 live The latest live news, sport, traffic, weather and comment from Wales Brecon Beacons soldier deaths: Further tests ordered as inquest rules cause of deaths 'unascertained' Life expectancy in poorest regions of Wales now seven years less than parts of England News Opinion Bethan Darwin on Confidentiality The only foolproof way of keeping confidentiality is not to tell anyone anything. If you can’t keep your own secrets you can’t expect anyone else to keep them either\" Emma Watkins on Welsh Government Given that 90% of all homes are built by the private sector, last week’s ministerial statement by housing minister Carl Sargeant marked a dramatic change of direction in government policy that should deliver a real boost to house building.\" Sport Latest Sport Rugby Football Cardiff City Swansea City Boxing Cricket Ice Hockey Other Sport Sport Opinion Trending Today Gareth Bale Sam Hammam Vincent Tan Andreas Cornelius Wilfried Bony Popular this week British and Irish Lions Wales Rugby Team Cardiff City FC Swansea City FC Sam Warburton Top Sport The greatest tries the Millennium Stadium has ever seen: Relive nearly 15 years of magical moments The Millennium Stadium has witnessed some remarkable tries since opening in 2009. Here, we fill the void of the rugby off-season by looking at the very best exclusive Life president Sam Hammam and his support role to Cardiff City owner Vincent Tan Tom Ince: Why I had to turn down £8m Cardiff City move Sport Opinion Gareth Rogers on Cardiff City's signings from abroad South Koren star Kim has been a revelation for Malky Mackay\" Terry Phillips on Sam Hammam's re-emergence at Cardiff City Say what you like about the Lebanese businessman, but he loves his football and has stayed in touch with City fans.\" What's On Latest What's On Find Things To Do Film & TV Music Restaurants & Bars Theatre Comedy What's On Opinion Trending Today Bruce Springsteen Paul McCartney Richard Burton Helena Bonham Carter Bryn Terfel Popular this week Restaurant reviews Katherine Jenkins Catherine Zeta-Jones Tom Jones Book reviews Top What's On Bruce Springsteen: The Boss rocks Cardiff's Millennium Stadium (pictures) The 63-year-old American legend pays his second visit to the city after his sell-out Magic tour in 2008     updated Review: Bruce Springsteen at Cardiff Millennium Stadium Bryn Terfel launches new company to support emerging classical music talent What's On Opinion Kathryn Williams on Bruce Springsteen In the days when 'performers' such as Rhianna feel like crotch grabbing and costume changes are enough - The Boss truly shows them how it's done\" Peter Collins on the Capital City Jazz Orchestra It was an entertaining evening of music-making with the band playing a selection of classics and more unusual numbers\" Lifestyle Latest Lifestyle Showbiz Fashion Food & Drink Welsh Homes Nostalgia Lifestyle Opinion Trending Today Roald Dahl Kate Middleton Tom Jones Anthony Hopkins Catherine Zeta-Jones Popular this week Welsh history Hay Festival Wales Book of the Year Beauty Book reviews Top Lifestyle James Dean Bradfield unveils plaque at reopening of Newbridge Memorial Hall and Institute The lead singer of Manic Street Preachers was at the Grade II-listed building to celebrate the completion of the first phase of a £2.9m Lottery funded refurbishment project Traders inspired by Mary Portas as they bid to regenerate their high street Gabby Logan: BBC boss scolded me over 'too glamorous' boots Lifestyle Opinion Abbie Wightwick on motherhood I’ve come prepared with a fistful of tissues and a camera. Shame I can’t see through my tears to focus on what’s happening\" Dan O'Neill on The NHS She got out of bed that morning as Miss Francesca Hogg. She went to bed that night as Dr Francesca Hogg. Her life had changed forever\" In Your Area North Wales Mid Wales South-East Wales South-West Wales Cardiff Swansea Anglesey Blaenau Gwent Bridgend Caerphilly Carmarthenshire Ceredigion Conwy Cynon Valley Denbighshire Flintshire Gwynedd Merthyr Tydfil Monmouthshire Neath Port Talbot Newport Pembrokeshire Powys Rhondda Pontypridd Torfaen Vale of Glamorgan Wrexham Buy, Sell & Tell Jobs Jobs Search for jobs in Wales Motors Motors Find new & used cars for sale Property Property Buying, Selling or Renting? Business Directory Business Directory Search our local business directory Family Notices Family Notices View latest announcements online Travel Travel Find and book your next holiday with us Dating Dating Looking for a date in Wales? Book an Ad Book an Ad Create Private and Trade ads BuySell BuySell Buy or sell 1000s of new and used items Search: Please provide search keyword(s) Hot Topic: Royal Welsh Show - Wales Book of the Year - Katherine Jenkins - Catherine Zeta-Jones Follow Us: Facebook Facebook WalesOnline The latest Wales news, sport, weather and events from Wales Online Wales Rugby News The home of all the latest news from the Welsh rugby scene. Cardiff City News All your Cardiff City news from the Wales Online sports desk. Swansea City News All your Swansea City news from the Wales Online sports desk. Twitter Follow us on Twitter @walesonline The latest Wales news, sport, weather and events from Wales Online @walesrugby Latest Welsh Rugby News from WalesOnline - Western Mail, South Wales Echo and Wales on Sunday @welsh_football All your Welsh football news from the Wales Online sports desk @yourcardiff The latest Cardiff news, business, crime and transport from WalesOnline Newsletters Subscribe Daily bulletin A daily bulletin of the best news and sport from WalesOnline Home What's On Music Music updated Review: Bruce Springsteen at Cardiff Millennium Stadium Bruce Springsteen 24 Jul 2013 The Boss and his E Street Band thrilled the crowds in an epic-length set that showcased his extensive back catalogue Bryn Terfel launches new company to support emerging classical music talent Bryn Terfel 24 Jul 2013 He's teamed up with his record label Deutsche Grammophon to create Snowdonia Records Bruce Springsteen Cardiff: Fans swarm the city streets Millennium Stadium Video 23 Jul 2013 updated Bruce Springsteen fans have swarmed to Cardiff in their thousands today to enjoy one of the last great rockstars in the summer sunshine The Voice star Alys Williams voice to appear at Merthyr’s annual street festival Merthyr Tydfil 23 Jul 2013 A star from hit TV show The Voice is set to take centre stage during Theatre Soar’s annual street festival. Fans queue for two days to secure spot at the front for Bruce Springsteen's Cardiff concert Bruce Springsteen Gallery Video 23 Jul 2013 updated Hundreds of fans prepared to endure hardship to be as close as they can to the Boss Manic Street Preachers unveil new single Show Me The Wonder Bruce Springsteen: Millennium Stadium queues already forming as fans seek front-row spots to watch The Boss News & Previews Bryn Terfel launches new company to support emerging classical music talent Bryn Terfel 24 Jul 2013 He's teamed up with his record label Deutsche Grammophon to create Snowdonia Records Bruce Springsteen Cardiff: Fans swarm the city streets Millennium Stadium Video 23 Jul 2013 updated Bruce Springsteen fans have swarmed to Cardiff in their thousands today to enjoy one of the last great rockstars in the summer sunshine The Voice star Alys Williams voice to appear at Merthyr’s annual street festival Merthyr Tydfil 23 Jul 2013 A star from hit TV show The Voice is set to take centre stage during Theatre Soar’s annual street festival. Fans queue for two days to secure spot at the front for Bruce Springsteen's Cardiff concert Bruce Springsteen Cardiff preview: The Boss brings his epic show to Cardiff Manic Street Preachers unveil new single Show Me The Wonder Reviews updated Review: Bruce Springsteen at Cardiff Millennium Stadium Bruce Springsteen 24 Jul 2013 * * * * * The Boss and his E Street Band thrilled the crowds in an epic-length set that showcased his extensive back catalogue Review: Tiddly Prom – Bert’s Magic Musical Farmyard, St David’s Hall, Cardiff New Theatre 22 Jul 2013 * * * * The children’s show staged each year as part of the wider Welsh Proms is produced by Arts Active Review: Martin Rossiter – Clwb Ifor Bach, Cardiff Music Video 24 Jun 2013 * * * * * Former Gene singer Martin has released his first solo album - a stunning collection of confessional and autobiographical torch songs accompanied by a solitary piano Review: BBC Cardiff Singer of the World, St David’s Hall, Cardiff Review: BBC National Orchestra of Wales, Hoddinott Hall, Cardiff Review: Wagner Dream, Wales Millennium Centre, Cardiff You Might Have Missed... Catatonia Cerys Matthews to direct music showcase Womex in Cardiff Showbiz Prog rocker Rob Reed on making the Celtic Dark Side Of The Moon Music ‘I’m not a musical theatre singer,' says tenor Alfie Boe Music Brothers singer Joel Hurst on memorable gigs and musical influences Best of Wales Music Videos on MUZU.TV. What's On   Find something to do tonight in your area Videos & Photos updated Review: Bruce Springsteen at Cardiff Millennium Stadium * * * * * Bruce Springsteen: The Boss rocks Cardiff's Millennium Stadium (pictures) updated Bruce Springsteen Cardiff: Fans swarm the city streets Cardiff 10k   Info and updates on the 2013 Cardiff 10k and Fun Run Most Recent What's On Film & TV What's on TV tonight: Who Do You Think You Are?, The Café and Love/Hate Bruce Springsteen Review: Bruce Springsteen at Cardiff Millennium Stadium Bryn Terfel Bryn Terfel launches new company to support emerging classical music talent Bruce Springsteen Bruce Springsteen: The Boss rocks Cardiff's Millennium Stadium (pictures) Millennium Stadium Bruce Springsteen Cardiff: Fans swarm the city streets Outdoor adventures for kids: the must-read list   Check out great days out for children in Wales Follow Us Contact Us Send A Story Advertise The Editor Journalists Join us on social media. For the latest local news straight to your Twitter, Facebook feed, e-mail inbox or tablet. Twitter @walesonline @walesrugby @welsh_football @yourcardiff Facebook WalesOnline Welsh Rugby News Cardiff City Swansea City E-Editions Download our e-editions here. Contact us Got a story in your area? Is there something happening in your area you would like us to report on? Email newsdesk@walesonline.co.uk Phone Newsdesk: 029 2024 3630 Advertising enquiries: 029 2024 4296 Postal Address WalesOnline, Media Wales, Six Park Street, Cardiff, CF10 1XR Contacts Newsdesk 029 2024 3630 newsdesk@walesonline.co.uk Head of Web: Paul Rowland 029 2024 3626 paul.rowland@walesonline.co.uk Picturedesk 029 2024 3649 rob.norman@walesonline.co.uk Photosales: Saffron Herbert 029 2024 4330 saffron.herbert@walesonline.co.uk Competitions and promotions: Victoria Gladwin 029 2024 4314 victoria.gladwin@walesonline.co.uk Work experience queries steffan.rhys@walesonline.co.uk Organised a special event? Tell us about it and, if possible, send us a picture Contact Pat English, David Prince and Katie Dowling Phone 029 2024 3620 or 029 2024 3622 Email communities@walesonline.co.uk Complaints WalesOnline.co.uk conforms to the newspaper industry's voluntary Code of Practice, administered by the Press Complaints Commission. If you feel we have made an error in a report, or have fallen below our usual high standards, please write in the first instance to: Ceri Gould, Online Editor, WalesOnline.co.uk, Media Wales, Six Park Street, Cardiff CF10 1XR. Tel: 029 2024 3672. Email: ceri.gould@mediawales.co.uk The PCC code of practice, along with details of how to complain, is available from Halton House, 20/23 High Holborn, London EC1N 2JD. Website www.pcc.org.uk or email complaints@pcc.org.uk telephone 020 7831 0022, helpline 0845 600 2757. Send a story Email newsdesk@walesonline.co.uk Phone 029 2024 2630 Postal Address Newsdesk, Media Wales, Six Park Street, Cardiff CF10 1XR Advertise with WalesOnline We reach over 1,384,563* unique users a month with dedicated coverage of all things Welsh. To book an advert with WalesOnline call 029 2024 4296, email pedr.roberts@walesonline.co.uk or visit Media Wales website for more information WalesOnline is part of Media Wales, publisher of the Western Mail, South Wales Echo, Wales on Sunday and the seven Celtic weekly titles, offering you unique access to our audience across Wales online and in print. The Editor Ceri Gould Editor, WalesOnline Email ceri.gould@walesonline.co.uk Ceri has been editor of WalesOnline since April 2012. She was previously executive editor of Media Wales and deputy editor of the Western Mail. She started her career on the Glamorgan Gazette. Journalists David Williamson Political Editor Martin Shipton Chief Reporter Peter Law Chief Reporter Clare Hutchinson Crime Correspondent Gareth Evans Education Correspondent Julia McWatt Health Editor Karen Price Arts Editor Sion Barry Business Editor Paul Abbandonato Head of Sport Chris Wathan Swansea City Correspondent Terry Phillips Cardiff City Correspondent Simon Thomas Rugby Correspondent Andy Howell Rugby Correspondent News Wales News Business UK News World News Crime Health Politics Education Farming News Opinion Sport Rugby Football Cardiff City Swansea City Boxing Ice Hockey Cricket Rugby League Tennis Golf Cycling Athletics Sport Opinion What's On Find Things To Do Film & TV Music Restaurants & Bars Theatre Comedy What's On Opinion Lifestyle Showbiz Fashion Food & Drink Welsh Homes Nostalgia Lifestyle Opinion In Your Area Anglesey Blaenau Gwent Bridgend Caerphilly Carmarthenshire Ceredigion Conwy Denbighshire Flintshire Gwynedd Merthyr Tydfil Monmouthshire Neath Port Talbot Newport Pembrokeshire Powys Rhondda Cynon Valley Pontypridd Torfaen Vale of Glamorgan Wrexham View All Locations Useful Links Contact Us About Us Subscriptions Download our e-editions Letters To The Editor Advertise with us Corrections & Clarifications Reader Panel Terms & Conditions Privacy Policy Cookie Policy RSS Feeds Buy, Sell & Tell Jobs Motors Property Business Directory Family Notices Travel Dating Book an Ad BuySell"]},
{
"id":"sha1:RXQ25MKYOGIESJWSZES5KXDCSHSPOPF5/2O7Vle2nkvYEmiq9Gd+dJA==",
"source_file":"BL-20130723050052741-00000-4204~opera~8443.warc.gz",
"source_file_offset":112563931,
"url":"http://www.walesonline.co.uk/whats-on/music/bruce-springsteen-cardiff-what-time-4407991",
"url_type":["normal"],
"record_type":"response",
"resourcename":["bruce-springsteen-cardiff-what-time-4407991"],
"host":"walesonline.co.uk",
"domain":"walesonline.co.uk",
"public_suffix":"co.uk",
"content_type_served":"text/html;charset=UTF-8",
"server":["Apache-Coyote/1.1"],
"content_length":154514,
"hash":["sha1:RXQ25MKYOGIESJWSZES5KXDCSHSPOPF5"],
"crawl_date":"2013-07-23T06:54:46Z",
"crawl_year":"2013",
"wayback_date":"20130723065446",
"wct_subjects":["Arts & Humanities",
"Society & Culture",
"News and Contemporary Events",
"Sports and Recreation",
"Communities"],
"collection":["100 Best Sites"],
"collections":["100 Best Sites",
"News Sites",
"News Sites|Web only news sites"],
"access_terms":["RRO"],
"content_text_length":16814,
"content_type":["text/html"],
"title":"Bruce Springsteen, Cardiff: What time is Bruce Springsteen on stage at the Cardiff Millennium Stadium? Travel advice, parking tips and more - Wales Online",
"keywords":["Millennium Stadium,Essential Wales,Cardiff,Bruce Springsteen"],
"content_encoding":"UTF-8",
"content_ffb":"3c21646f",
"content_type_droid":"text/html; version=5",
"links_domains":["bookanad.com",
"newmarket.travel",
"facebook.com",
"pcc.org.uk",
"muzu.tv",
"icnetwork.co.uk",
"mediawales.co.uk",
"twitter.com",
"jobswales.co.uk",
"walesonline.co.uk"],
"links_public_suffixes":["org.uk",
"com",
"tv",
"co.uk",
"travel"],
"elements_used":["dt",
"body",
"link",
"div",
"img",
"noscript",
"figcaption",
"br",
"meta",
"dd",
"time",
"title",
"figure",
"link/@rel=stylesheet",
"style",
"link/@rel=pingback",
"h5",
"dl",
"h4",
"ol",
"h1",
"head",
"h3",
"h2",
"ul",
"form",
"a",
"blockquote",
"label",
"script",
"header",
"footer",
"scr'+'ipt",
"li",
"link/@rel=canonical",
"link/@rel=alternate",
"input",
"iframe",
"strong",
"p",
"nav",
"html",
"link/@rel=dns-prefetch",
"span"],
"content_type_tika":"text/html; charset=UTF-8",
"content_type_version":"5",
"content_type_full":"text/html; charset=UTF-8; version=5",
"content_type_norm":"html",
"content_language":"en",
"ssdeep_hash_bs_384":"rVyJ29CDThADqFFX3U/9nbxCjFpY04/9zerFNsO3/Gylo",
"ssdeep_hash_bs_768":"rGThADqFFX3+ZbZ/9zqHsO3uylo",
"ssdeep_hash_ngram_bs_384":"rVyJ29CDThADqFFX3U/9nbxCjFpY04/9zerFNsO3/Gylo",
"ssdeep_hash_ngram_bs_768":"rGThADqFFX3+ZbZ/9zqHsO3uylo",
"crawl_dates":["2013-07-23T06:54:46Z"],
"crawl_years":["2013"],
"_version_":1569733263651504128,
"type":"Other",
"content":["Jobs Motors Property Business Directory Family Notices Travel Dating Book an Ad BuySell Subscriptions Contact Us How we use Cookies Your Account Edit Profile Logout Wales Online 5 day forecast » Home News Latest News Wales News Business UK News World News Crime Politics Health Education Farming News Opinion Trending Today Kate Middleton The Queen Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh Prince Charles, Prince of Wales David Cameron Popular this week Letters to the Editor British and Irish Lions Politics Warren Gatland Sam Warburton Top News Live: Wales breaking news, Tuesday 23 July, 2013 live The latest live news, sport, traffic, weather and comment from Wales Royal baby news: Kate Middleton and Prince William wait to introduce new baby boy to the world Royal baby: Welsh joy at birth of a son for William and Kate News Opinion David Williamson on electioneering For Conservatives to have any hope of winning in target ares such as Delyn, Derby and Dudley they must acknowledge what a torrid half-decade it has been for many families\" Dan O'Neill on How a five-year-old saved one of the world's great movie studios Then in 1941 she got her first screen kiss and that, really, was the end. No-one wanted a grown-up Shirley Temple\" Sport Latest Sport Rugby Football Cardiff City Swansea City Boxing Cricket Ice Hockey Other Sport Sport Opinion Trending Today Vincent Tan Sam Hammam Dave Brailsford Geraint Thomas Steve Borley Popular this week British and Irish Lions Wales Rugby Team Cardiff City FC Swansea City FC Sam Warburton Top Sport Cardiff City not in the market for new strikers as Malky Mackay puts faith in current frontmen Cardiff manager Mackay is happy with his attacking options and will not sign another striker this summer unless 'something incredible comes along' Swansea City star Nathan Dyer in talks to tie up new contract at Liberty Stadium Mike Phillips determined to still be Wales' number one until 2015 Rugby World Cup Sport Opinion Terry Phillips on Cardiff City's pre-season training tour in Switzerland Bellamy was a front-runner and Kevin McNaughton impressed time and again\" Chris Wathan on Jonathan De Guzman's place in Swansea City's team What is not straightforward is just who is in Laudrup’s mind when it comes to his midfield three\" What's On Latest What's On Find Things To Do Film & TV Music Restaurants & Bars Theatre Comedy What's On Opinion Trending Today Bruce Springsteen Katherine Jenkins Justin Bieber Dave Brailsford Geraint Thomas Popular this week Restaurant reviews Katherine Jenkins Catherine Zeta-Jones Tom Jones Book reviews Top What's On Fans queue for two days to secure spot at the front for Bruce Springsteen's Cardiff concert Hundreds of fans prepared to endure hardship to be as close as they can to the Boss Bruce Springsteen Cardiff preview: The Boss brings his epic show to Cardiff Manic Street Preachers unveil new single Show Me The Wonder What's On Opinion Karen Price on the cult musical My Name Is Sue Full of energy and humour, it was also surprisingly touching in places... Edinburgh audiences are in for another treat.\" Nathan Bevan on Luther Luther and Stark went toe to toe and tried to out alpha male each other with a conversation about extreme weather conditions\" Lifestyle Latest Lifestyle Showbiz Fashion Food & Drink Welsh Homes Nostalgia Lifestyle Opinion Trending Today Bruce Springsteen Kate Middleton Catherine Zeta-Jones Anthony Hopkins Geraint Thomas Popular this week Welsh history Hay Festival Wales Book of the Year Beauty Book reviews Top Lifestyle Gabby Logan: BBC boss scolded me over 'too glamorous' boots TV presenter Gabby, 40,  has defended her glossy on-screen appearance after revealing she was told off for her high-heeled footwear updated Royal Welsh Show: Hopes for record crowds at Llanelwedd if weather holds English Youth Ballet dancers perform for patients at Wales' children's hospital Lifestyle Opinion Peter Collins on The Ashes Strangely, it was not much fun watching our boys thrashing the lads from Down Under at the Home of Cricket. One would have wished for more of a competition.\" Graham Henry on Royal Baby I can objectively say that Royal fever has reached a point that borders on alarming\" In Your Area North Wales Mid Wales South-East Wales South-West Wales Cardiff Swansea Anglesey Blaenau Gwent Bridgend Caerphilly Carmarthenshire Ceredigion Conwy Cynon Valley Denbighshire Flintshire Gwynedd Merthyr Tydfil Monmouthshire Neath Port Talbot Newport Pembrokeshire Powys Rhondda Pontypridd Torfaen Vale of Glamorgan Wrexham Buy, Sell & Tell Jobs Jobs Search for jobs in Wales Motors Motors Find new & used cars for sale Property Property Buying, Selling or Renting? Business Directory Business Directory Search our local business directory Family Notices Family Notices View latest announcements online Travel Travel Find and book your next holiday with us Dating Dating Looking for a date in Wales? Book an Ad Book an Ad Create Private and Trade ads BuySell BuySell Buy or sell 1000s of new and used items Search: Please provide search keyword(s) Hot Topic: Royal Welsh Show - Wales Book of the Year - Katherine Jenkins - Catherine Zeta-Jones Follow Us: Facebook Facebook WalesOnline The latest Wales news, sport, weather and events from Wales Online Wales Rugby News The home of all the latest news from the Welsh rugby scene. Cardiff City News All your Cardiff City news from the Wales Online sports desk. Swansea City News All your Swansea City news from the Wales Online sports desk. Twitter Follow us on Twitter @walesonline The latest Wales news, sport, weather and events from Wales Online @walesrugby Latest Welsh Rugby News from WalesOnline - Western Mail, South Wales Echo and Wales on Sunday @welsh_football All your Welsh football news from the Wales Online sports desk @yourcardiff The latest Cardiff news, business, crime and transport from WalesOnline Newsletters Subscribe Daily bulletin A daily bulletin of the best news and sport from WalesOnline Home What's On Music Essential Wales By Richard Beech Comments Bruce Springsteen, Cardiff: What time is Bruce Springsteen on stage at the Cardiff Millennium Stadium? Travel advice, parking tips and more 18 Jun 2013 17:33 Bruce Springsteen hits Cardiff on July 23, bringing his epic show to the Millennium Stadium, but what time is he on? Bruce Springsteen Bruce Springsteen's Wrecking Ball Tour will have spanned for well over a year when he heads to Cardiff to perform at the Millennium Stadium. But what time will Bruce Springsteen hit the stage in Cardiff, and where should you park and how should you travel if you are heading to the show from outside of Cardiff? Luckily, if there's one certainty in life, it's that Bruce Springsteen will play his show for at least three hours, sometimes even four hours, and to have enough time to do this, the Boss has to start the show relatively early. The official show start time is 7:00pm, although the printed start time is usually 30 minutes to an hour earlier than when the artist takes to the stage. Fans can certainly expect Bruce and the E Street Band to the hit the stage between 7:00pm-8:00pm. Last time Bruce Springsteen performed in Cardiff, he broke the curfew to play and extended encore, so he's no stranger to playing bumper shows in the Welsh capital. What time does Bruce Springsteen go on stage at the Millennium Stadium in Cardiff? Stage times for the July 23 show have not yet been announced, but most likely: Between 7:00pm-8:00pm View gallery \" \" \" \" \" \" \" \" \" \" Bruce Springsteen on tour View gallery  It's likely that Bruce will play around 30 songs in his set, and that the show will finish between 11:00pm and midnight. The official 'doors' time is yet to be confirmed, but the Millennium Stadium opened doors for Rihanna's recent gig at 4:30pm, so we would advise fans to turn up for a similar doors time. Parking and transport into Cardiff is likely to be under immense strain on July 23, so we would advise parking outside of the city centre. This will also ensure that you are not stuck in city centre traffic after the gig. There are a number of places to park in Cardiff Bay, around a 15-20 minute walk from the centre, or a very short taxi ride (approximately £5). Road closures will be in place in the town centre, although these have not yet been confirmed, and it is likely that Cardiff Central Station will employ the use of its event day queueing system, which forces commuters to wait outside the station in queues separated into rail destinations. Extra trains will most likely be laid on, but the queues will still be lengthy, make sure you make a mental note of where you should be queueing when you arrive in Cardiff at the station before the gig, as the signs will already be in place. Food is available in this area (near the train station), so it's a good time to grab a bite to eat while you wait for your train.   Recently Published Bruce Springsteen Cardiff preview: The Boss brings his epic show to Cardiff The Boss is set to wow Cardiff with his world-renowned show, and is expected to play for up to four hours at the Millennium Stadium Bruce Springsteen Cardiff: The Boss is coming soon, and we have travel info, parking, stage times, rumours, and much more Bruce Springsteen: Millennium Stadium queues already forming as fans seek front-row spots to watch The Boss Previous Articles 10 great things to do in Wales this month - April 2013 We round up the best things to do in Wales in April 2013, from all corners of the country, we've picked the best events going on this month Don't look down: Millennium Stadium maintenance gets underway on 90 metre masts What time is Rihanna's concert in Cardiff, Millennium Stadium? Door opening times, show times, and info on when Rihanna is on stage in Cardiff Related Tags Places Cardiff People Bruce Springsteen Organisations Millennium Stadium In The News Essential Wales Best of Wales Music Videos on MUZU.TV. See more stories you'll love You've turned off story recommendations. Turn them on and we'll update the list below with stories we think you'll love (how we do this). Recommended in What's On Why? Bruce Springsteen Fans queue for two days to secure spot at the front for Bruce Springsteen's Cardiff concert Millennium Stadium Bruce Springsteen Cardiff preview: The Boss brings his epic show to Cardiff Festival Number Six Manic Street Preachers unveil new single Show Me The Wonder Bruce Springsteen Bruce Springsteen: Millennium Stadium queues already forming as fans seek front-row spots to watch The Boss Katherine Jenkins Katherine Jenkins' Twitter account hacked by Selena Gomez fan Catherine Zeta-Jones Catherine Zeta-Jones: Family and health take pride of place for me now BBC JLS and Little Mix wow thousands who flock to Ponty's Big Weekend What's On   Find something to do tonight in your area Most Read in What's On Millennium Stadium Bruce Springsteen Cardiff preview: The Boss brings his epic show to Cardiff Bruce Springsteen Bruce Springsteen: Millennium Stadium queues already forming as fans seek front-row spots to watch The Boss Festival Number Six Manic Street Preachers unveil new single Show Me The Wonder Richard Burton Exploring Richard Burton and Elizabeth Taylor's chemistry on and off-screen Essential Wales Bruce Springsteen, Cardiff: What time is Bruce Springsteen on stage at the Cardiff Millennium Stadium? Travel advice, parking tips and more Cardiff 10k   Info and updates on the 2013 Cardiff 10k and Fun Run See more stories you'll love You've turned off story recommendations. Turn them on and we'll update the list below with stories we think you'll love (how we do this). Recommended Why? News Live: Wales breaking news, Tuesday 23 July, 2013 The Ashes The Ashes: 'True sport is not all about winning' Bruce Springsteen Fans queue for two days to secure spot at the front for Bruce Springsteen's Cardiff concert David Cameron David Cameron’s crackdown on net porn welcomed in Wales BBC Gabby Logan: BBC boss scolded me over 'too glamorous' boots Horsemeat scandal Farmers' leaders criticise the lack of any prosecutions over the horsemeat scandal Conservative Party David Williamson: Sometimes it takes chutzpah for political parties to make real progress CBI Cabbies in line for training and branded uniforms to boost capital's image Cardiff Council Cardiff Business Council set up to promote economy of the capital Welsh Government Welsh Government to relax planning rules for homeowners Outdoor adventures for kids: the must-read list   Check out great days out for children in Wales Find a local business   Search for local businesses in your area Nostalgia   Check out brilliant pictures from our archives Follow Us Contact Us Send A Story Advertise The Editor Journalists Join us on social media. For the latest local news straight to your Twitter, Facebook feed, e-mail inbox or tablet. Twitter @walesonline @walesrugby @welsh_football @yourcardiff Facebook WalesOnline Welsh Rugby News Cardiff City Swansea City E-Editions Download our e-editions here. Contact us Got a story in your area? Is there something happening in your area you would like us to report on? Email newsdesk@walesonline.co.uk Phone 029 2024 3630 Postal Address WalesOnline, Media Wales, Six Park Street, Cardiff, CF10 1XR Contacts Newsdesk 029 2024 3630 newsdesk@walesonline.co.uk Head of Web: Paul Rowland 029 2024 3626 paul.rowland@walesonline.co.uk Picturedesk 029 2024 3649 rob.norman@walesonline.co.uk Photosales: Saffron Herbert 029 2024 4330 saffron.herbert@walesonline.co.uk Competitions and promotions: Victoria Gladwin 029 2024 4314 victoria.gladwin@walesonline.co.uk Work experience queries steffan.rhys@walesonline.co.uk Organised a special event? Tell us about it and, if possible, send us a picture Contact Pat English Phone 029 2024 3680 Email pat.english@walesonline.co.uk Complaints WalesOnline.co.uk conforms to the newspaper industry's voluntary Code of Practice, administered by the Press Complaints Commission. If you feel we have made an error in a report, or have fallen below our usual high standards, please write in the first instance to: Ceri Gould, Online Editor, WalesOnline.co.uk, Media Wales, Six Park Street, Cardiff CF10 1XR. Tel: 029 2024 3672. Email: ceri.gould@mediawales.co.uk The PCC code of practice, along with details of how to complain, is available from Halton House, 20/23 High Holborn, London EC1N 2JD. Website www.pcc.org.uk or email complaints@pcc.org.uk telephone 020 7831 0022, helpline 0845 600 2757. Send a story Email newsdesk@walesonline.co.uk Phone 029 2024 2630 Postal Address Newsdesk, Media Wales, Six Park Street, Cardiff CF10 1XR Advertise with WalesOnline We reach over 1,384,563* unique users a month with dedicated coverage of all things Welsh. To book an advert with WalesOnline call 029 2024 4296, email pedr.roberts@walesonline.co.uk or visit Media Wales website for more information WalesOnline is part of Media Wales, publisher of the Western Mail, South Wales Echo, Wales on Sunday and the seven Celtic weekly titles, offering you unique access to our audience across Wales online and in print. The Editor Ceri Gould Editor, WalesOnline Email ceri.gould@walesonline.co.uk Ceri has been editor of WalesOnline since April 2012. She was previously executive editor of Media Wales and deputy editor of the Western Mail. She started her career on the Glamorgan Gazette. Journalists David Williamson Political Editor Martin Shipton Chief Reporter Peter Law Chief Reporter Clare Hutchinson Crime Correspondent Gareth Evans Education Correspondent Julia McWatt Health Editor Karen Price Arts Editor Sion Barry Business Editor Paul Abbandonato Head of Sport Chris Wathan Swansea City Correspondent Terry Phillips Cardiff City Correspondent Simon Thomas Rugby Correspondent Andy Howell Rugby Correspondent News Wales News Business UK News World News Crime Health Politics Education Farming News Opinion Sport Rugby Football Cardiff City Swansea City Boxing Ice Hockey Cricket Rugby League Tennis Golf Cycling Athletics Sport Opinion What's On Find Things To Do Film & TV Music Restaurants & Bars Theatre Comedy What's On Opinion Lifestyle Showbiz Fashion Food & Drink Welsh Homes Nostalgia Lifestyle Opinion In Your Area Anglesey Blaenau Gwent Bridgend Caerphilly Carmarthenshire Ceredigion Conwy Denbighshire Flintshire Gwynedd Merthyr Tydfil Monmouthshire Neath Port Talbot Newport Pembrokeshire Powys Rhondda Cynon Valley Pontypridd Torfaen Vale of Glamorgan Wrexham View All Locations Useful Links Contact Us About Us Subscriptions Download our e-editions Letters To The Editor Advertise with us Corrections & Clarifications Reader Panel Terms & Conditions Privacy Policy Cookie Policy RSS Feeds Buy, Sell & Tell Jobs Motors Property Business Directory Family Notices Travel Dating Book an Ad BuySell"]},
{
"id":"sha1:IX5VFQQDXKIEMQ3NODMBCECSNQ4Y5JNN/subgryC2VUwzoREAK/QX8g==",
"source_file":"BL-20130723050052741-00000-4204~opera~8443.warc.gz",
"source_file_offset":559852343,
"url":"http://www.walesonline.co.uk/whats-on/theatre/review-sherlock-holmes-best-kept-4570950",
"url_type":["normal"],
"record_type":"response",
"resourcename":["review-sherlock-holmes-best-kept-4570950"],
"host":"walesonline.co.uk",
"domain":"walesonline.co.uk",
"public_suffix":"co.uk",
"content_type_served":"text/html;charset=UTF-8",
"server":["Apache-Coyote/1.1"],
"content_length":146647,
"hash":["sha1:IX5VFQQDXKIEMQ3NODMBCECSNQ4Y5JNN"],
"crawl_date":"2013-07-23T14:52:11Z",
"crawl_year":"2013",
"wayback_date":"20130723145211",
"wct_subjects":["Arts & Humanities",
"Society & Culture",
"News and Contemporary Events",
"Sports and Recreation",
"Communities"],
"collection":["100 Best Sites"],
"collections":["100 Best Sites",
"News Sites",
"News Sites|Web only news sites"],
"access_terms":["RRO"],
"content_text_length":15956,
"content_type":["text/html"],
"title":"Review: Sherlock Holmes: The Best Kept Secret, New Theatre, Cardiff - Alison Sanders - Wales Online",
"keywords":["Sherlock,Benedict Cumberbatch,New Theatre,Cardiff"],
"content_encoding":"UTF-8",
"content_ffb":"3c21646f",
"content_type_droid":"text/html; version=5",
"links_domains":["bookanad.com",
"newmarket.travel",
"facebook.com",
"pcc.org.uk",
"muzu.tv",
"icnetwork.co.uk",
"mediawales.co.uk",
"twitter.com",
"jobswales.co.uk",
"newtheatrecardiff.co.uk",
"walesonline.co.uk"],
"links_public_suffixes":["org.uk",
"com",
"tv",
"co.uk",
"travel"],
"elements_used":["dt",
"body",
"link",
"div",
"img",
"noscript",
"figcaption",
"br",
"meta",
"dd",
"time",
"title",
"figure",
"link/@rel=stylesheet",
"style",
"link/@rel=pingback",
"h5",
"dl",
"h4",
"ol",
"h1",
"head",
"h3",
"h2",
"ul",
"form",
"a",
"blockquote",
"label",
"script",
"header",
"footer",
"scr'+'ipt",
"li",
"link/@rel=canonical",
"link/@rel=alternate",
"input",
"iframe",
"strong",
"p",
"nav",
"html",
"link/@rel=dns-prefetch",
"span"],
"content_type_tika":"text/html; charset=UTF-8",
"content_type_version":"5",
"content_type_full":"text/html; charset=UTF-8; version=5",
"content_type_norm":"html",
"content_language":"en",
"ssdeep_hash_bs_384":"rrT3moTDRV3B9LJG0rvhVgwOkJB/tqIqeQpmzz3uz",
"ssdeep_hash_bs_768":"rrTzV3B9LJG0rZ5JNtqzjQz3uz",
"ssdeep_hash_ngram_bs_384":"rrT3moTDRV3B9LJG0rvhVgwOkJB/tqIqeQpmzz3uz",
"ssdeep_hash_ngram_bs_768":"rrTzV3B9LJG0rZ5JNtqzjQz3uz",
"crawl_dates":["2013-07-23T14:52:11Z"],
"crawl_years":["2013"],
"_version_":1569733276533260288,
"type":"Other",
"content":["Jobs Motors Property Business Directory Family Notices Travel Dating Book an Ad BuySell Subscriptions Contact Us How we use Cookies Your Account Edit Profile Logout Wales Online 5 day forecast » Home News Latest News Wales News Business UK News World News Crime Politics Health Education Farming News Opinion Trending Today Kate Middleton Prince Charles, Prince of Wales The Queen Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh David Davies MP Popular this week Letters to the Editor British and Irish Lions Politics Warren Gatland Sam Warburton Top News Live: Wales breaking news, Tuesday 23 July, 2013 live The latest live news, sport, traffic, weather and comment from Wales Royal baby news: Wait continues for first glimpse of Kate Middleton and Prince William's new baby Population of Wales' cities to rocket as number of people living in poorer areas shrinks News Opinion Sion Barry on the future for Cardiff Airport The Welsh Government has its own plans for the long-term development of Cardiff\" David Williamson on electioneering For Conservatives to have any hope of winning in target ares such as Delyn, Derby and Dudley they must acknowledge what a torrid half-decade it has been for many families\" Sport Latest Sport Rugby Football Cardiff City Swansea City Boxing Cricket Ice Hockey Other Sport Sport Opinion Trending Today Vincent Tan Sam Hammam Steve Borley Brendan Rodgers Huw Jenkins Popular this week British and Irish Lions Wales Rugby Team Cardiff City FC Swansea City FC Sam Warburton Top Sport Swansea City tie up £12m signing of Ivory Coast star Wilfried Bony after completing work permit Former Vitesse Arnhem striker Wilfried Bony is now officially a Swan after completing his complicated work permit Cardiff City targetting Toulouse midfielder Etienne Capoue, according to reports Racing Metro deny move for Lions and Wales star Leigh Halfpenny Sport Opinion Terry Phillips on Cardiff City's pre-season training tour in Switzerland Bellamy was a front-runner and Kevin McNaughton impressed time and again\" Chris Wathan on Jonathan De Guzman's place in Swansea City's team What is not straightforward is just who is in Laudrup’s mind when it comes to his midfield three\" What's On Latest What's On Find Things To Do Film & TV Music Restaurants & Bars Theatre Comedy What's On Opinion Trending Today Bruce Springsteen Richard Burton Helena Bonham Carter Katherine Jenkins Dylan Thomas Popular this week Restaurant reviews Katherine Jenkins Catherine Zeta-Jones Tom Jones Book reviews Top What's On Bruce Springsteen Cardiff: Fans swarm the city streets updated Bruce Springsteen fans have swarmed to Cardiff in their thousands today to enjoy one of the last great rockstars in the summer sunshine Review: Burton And Taylor on BBC Four updated Fans queue for two days to secure spot at the front for Bruce Springsteen's Cardiff concert What's On Opinion Peter Collins on the Capital City Jazz Orchestra It was an entertaining evening of music-making with the band playing a selection of classics and more unusual numbers\" Alison Stokes on 9 To 5 The Musical Like Parton herself, 9 To 5 The Musical is unpretentious, unashamed fun\" Lifestyle Latest Lifestyle Showbiz Fashion Food & Drink Welsh Homes Nostalgia Lifestyle Opinion Trending Today Bruce Springsteen Kate Middleton Richard Burton Catherine Zeta-Jones Anthony Hopkins Popular this week Welsh history Hay Festival Wales Book of the Year Beauty Book reviews Top Lifestyle Gabby Logan: BBC boss scolded me over 'too glamorous' boots TV presenter Gabby, 40,  has defended her glossy on-screen appearance after revealing she was told off for her high-heeled footwear live Live: A day in the life of Hannah Jones, supplements & Week End magazine editor updated Royal Welsh Show: Hopes for record crowds at Llanelwedd if weather holds Lifestyle Opinion Peter Collins on The Ashes Strangely, it was not much fun watching our boys thrashing the lads from Down Under at the Home of Cricket. One would have wished for more of a competition.\" Graham Henry on Royal Baby I can objectively say that Royal fever has reached a point that borders on alarming\" In Your Area North Wales Mid Wales South-East Wales South-West Wales Cardiff Swansea Anglesey Blaenau Gwent Bridgend Caerphilly Carmarthenshire Ceredigion Conwy Cynon Valley Denbighshire Flintshire Gwynedd Merthyr Tydfil Monmouthshire Neath Port Talbot Newport Pembrokeshire Powys Rhondda Pontypridd Torfaen Vale of Glamorgan Wrexham Buy, Sell & Tell Jobs Jobs Search for jobs in Wales Motors Motors Find new & used cars for sale Property Property Buying, Selling or Renting? Business Directory Business Directory Search our local business directory Family Notices Family Notices View latest announcements online Travel Travel Find and book your next holiday with us Dating Dating Looking for a date in Wales? Book an Ad Book an Ad Create Private and Trade ads BuySell BuySell Buy or sell 1000s of new and used items Search: Please provide search keyword(s) Hot Topic: Royal Welsh Show - Wales Book of the Year - Katherine Jenkins - Catherine Zeta-Jones Follow Us: Facebook Facebook WalesOnline The latest Wales news, sport, weather and events from Wales Online Wales Rugby News The home of all the latest news from the Welsh rugby scene. Cardiff City News All your Cardiff City news from the Wales Online sports desk. Swansea City News All your Swansea City news from the Wales Online sports desk. Twitter Follow us on Twitter @walesonline The latest Wales news, sport, weather and events from Wales Online @walesrugby Latest Welsh Rugby News from WalesOnline - Western Mail, South Wales Echo and Wales on Sunday @welsh_football All your Welsh football news from the Wales Online sports desk @yourcardiff The latest Cardiff news, business, crime and transport from WalesOnline Newsletters Subscribe Daily bulletin A daily bulletin of the best news and sport from WalesOnline Home What's On Theatre New Theatre Comments By Alison Sanders Review: Sherlock Holmes: The Best Kept Secret, New Theatre, Cardiff 19 Jun 2013 13:11 This new story based on the adventures of Sherlock and Watson adds to recent Holmes interpretations to make it the ultimate whodunnit Alison Sanders **** Jason Durr and right Andrew Hall in Sherlock Holmes: The Best Kept Secret Forget Benedict Cumberbatch and Martin Freeman, there’s a new duo in town. The Best Kept Secret is a new story based on the adventures of Sherlock and Watson. Bafta-nominated Mark Catley picks up the story of Holmes’ confrontation with his nemesis Professor Moriarty at the Reichenbach Falls in one of Sir Arthur Conan Doyle’s famous books. The play opens three years on and sees Holmes working with loyal sidekick Watson on another intricate case which cleverly and sophisticatedly keeps you guessing until the very end. Director Nikolai Foster retains Doyle’s setting of Victorian England with cobbled paths, the darkness of the Ripper-era and careful lighting which adds to the mystery of the duo’s task. Catley and Foster have obviously drawn on the phenomenal success of the BBC’s hit series starring Cumberbatch and Freeman which offers a modern twist on Doyle’s famous stories. The dialogue has been written to be more contemporary and it works, offering a good share of humour along the way. But Foster is careful to keep Doyle’s legacy and the tradition of Sherlock Holmes by incorporating aspects of the original character – complete with deerstalker and pipe. The music is a fantastic addition to the suspense and excitement of the dialogue – a real credit to composer Grant Olding. Jason Durr plays an interesting and thoughtful Holmes as Catley offers an increased insight into the detective’s past and develops the relationship with Irene Alder known as ‘the woman’ and played by Tanya Franks. Television favourites Andrew Hall and Adrian Lukis are tremendous as reliable Dr Watson and Sherlock’s dysfunctional brother Mycroft. Entertaining and exciting, The Best Kept Secret runs on the success of recent Sherlock Holmes interpretations but adds to it making it the ultimate whodunnit and a must-see for Sherlock fanatics. Sherlock Holmes: The Best Kept Secret is at the New Theatre in Cardiff until Saturday. For tickets, call 029 2087 8889 or visit www.newtheatrecardiff.co.uk   Recently Published Elementary role for Rhys Ifans as he stars at Sherlock's big brother Rhys will appear in the first episode of the second series of the hit US TV show Elementary as Mycroft Holmes How Wales became a centre of excellence for TV production Doctor Who: The day Prince Charles became a Dalek Previous Articles Sherlock stars Benedict Cumberbatch and Martin Freeman spotted filming in Cardiff The stars of the hit BBC show were seen filming at Cardiff University's Glamorgan Building in the city centre Spooky thriller is the latest film venture for Sherlock and Star Trek star Benedict Judge Cameron on alcohol decision Related Tags Places Cardiff People Benedict Cumberbatch Entertainment Sherlock New Theatre Best of Wales Music Videos on MUZU.TV. See more stories you'll love You've turned off story recommendations. Turn them on and we'll update the list below with stories we think you'll love (how we do this). Recommended in What's On Why? Millennium Stadium Bruce Springsteen Cardiff: Fans swarm the city streets Bruce Springsteen Fans queue for two days to secure spot at the front for Bruce Springsteen's Cardiff concert Film & TV What's on TV tonight: Rachel Bruno: My Dad and Me, Kirstie’s Fill Your House For Free and Holby City Millennium Stadium Bruce Springsteen Cardiff preview: The Boss brings his epic show to Cardiff Festival Number Six Manic Street Preachers unveil new single Show Me The Wonder Bruce Springsteen Bruce Springsteen: Millennium Stadium queues already forming as fans seek front-row spots to watch The Boss Katherine Jenkins Katherine Jenkins' Twitter account hacked by Selena Gomez fan What's On   Find something to do tonight in your area Most Read in What's On Millennium Stadium Bruce Springsteen Cardiff preview: The Boss brings his epic show to Cardiff Bruce Springsteen Fans queue for two days to secure spot at the front for Bruce Springsteen's Cardiff concert Bruce Springsteen Bruce Springsteen: Millennium Stadium queues already forming as fans seek front-row spots to watch The Boss Essential Wales Bruce Springsteen, Cardiff: What time is Bruce Springsteen on stage at the Cardiff Millennium Stadium? Travel advice, parking tips and more Millennium Stadium Bruce Springsteen Cardiff: Fans swarm the city streets See more stories you'll love You've turned off story recommendations. Turn them on and we'll update the list below with stories we think you'll love (how we do this). Recommended Why? News Live: Wales breaking news, Tuesday 23 July, 2013 Cardiff Population of Wales' cities to rocket as number of people living in poorer areas shrinks Football News Swansea City tie up £12m signing of Ivory Coast star Wilfried Bony after completing work permit In The News Work to start on tribute park to tragic Welsh boy Harry Lifestyle Live: A day in the life of Hannah Jones, Supplements & Week End magazine editor Millennium Stadium Bruce Springsteen Cardiff: Fans swarm the city streets Crime Man arrested after 17-hour overnight siege at his Cardiff house Andre Villas Boas Manchester United have to act fast to land Gareth Bale as Read Madrid close in, say reports Cardiff Airport Cardiff Airport must move back into profit before considering selling any equity stake Bruce Springsteen Fans queue for two days to secure spot at the front for Bruce Springsteen's Cardiff concert Outdoor adventures for kids: the must-read list   Check out great days out for children in Wales Find a local business   Search for local businesses in your area Nostalgia   Check out brilliant pictures from our archives Follow Us Contact Us Send A Story Advertise The Editor Journalists Join us on social media. For the latest local news straight to your Twitter, Facebook feed, e-mail inbox or tablet. Twitter @walesonline @walesrugby @welsh_football @yourcardiff Facebook WalesOnline Welsh Rugby News Cardiff City Swansea City E-Editions Download our e-editions here. Contact us Got a story in your area? Is there something happening in your area you would like us to report on? Email newsdesk@walesonline.co.uk Phone 029 2024 3630 Postal Address WalesOnline, Media Wales, Six Park Street, Cardiff, CF10 1XR Contacts Newsdesk 029 2024 3630 newsdesk@walesonline.co.uk Head of Web: Paul Rowland 029 2024 3626 paul.rowland@walesonline.co.uk Picturedesk 029 2024 3649 rob.norman@walesonline.co.uk Photosales: Saffron Herbert 029 2024 4330 saffron.herbert@walesonline.co.uk Competitions and promotions: Victoria Gladwin 029 2024 4314 victoria.gladwin@walesonline.co.uk Work experience queries steffan.rhys@walesonline.co.uk Organised a special event? Tell us about it and, if possible, send us a picture Contact Pat English Phone 029 2024 3680 Email pat.english@walesonline.co.uk Complaints WalesOnline.co.uk conforms to the newspaper industry's voluntary Code of Practice, administered by the Press Complaints Commission. If you feel we have made an error in a report, or have fallen below our usual high standards, please write in the first instance to: Ceri Gould, Online Editor, WalesOnline.co.uk, Media Wales, Six Park Street, Cardiff CF10 1XR. Tel: 029 2024 3672. Email: ceri.gould@mediawales.co.uk The PCC code of practice, along with details of how to complain, is available from Halton House, 20/23 High Holborn, London EC1N 2JD. Website www.pcc.org.uk or email complaints@pcc.org.uk telephone 020 7831 0022, helpline 0845 600 2757. Send a story Email newsdesk@walesonline.co.uk Phone 029 2024 2630 Postal Address Newsdesk, Media Wales, Six Park Street, Cardiff CF10 1XR Advertise with WalesOnline We reach over 1,384,563* unique users a month with dedicated coverage of all things Welsh. To book an advert with WalesOnline call 029 2024 4296, email pedr.roberts@walesonline.co.uk or visit Media Wales website for more information WalesOnline is part of Media Wales, publisher of the Western Mail, South Wales Echo, Wales on Sunday and the seven Celtic weekly titles, offering you unique access to our audience across Wales online and in print. The Editor Ceri Gould Editor, WalesOnline Email ceri.gould@walesonline.co.uk Ceri has been editor of WalesOnline since April 2012. She was previously executive editor of Media Wales and deputy editor of the Western Mail. She started her career on the Glamorgan Gazette. Journalists David Williamson Political Editor Martin Shipton Chief Reporter Peter Law Chief Reporter Clare Hutchinson Crime Correspondent Gareth Evans Education Correspondent Julia McWatt Health Editor Karen Price Arts Editor Sion Barry Business Editor Paul Abbandonato Head of Sport Chris Wathan Swansea City Correspondent Terry Phillips Cardiff City Correspondent Simon Thomas Rugby Correspondent Andy Howell Rugby Correspondent News Wales News Business UK News World News Crime Health Politics Education Farming News Opinion Sport Rugby Football Cardiff City Swansea City Boxing Ice Hockey Cricket Rugby League Tennis Golf Cycling Athletics Sport Opinion What's On Find Things To Do Film & TV Music Restaurants & Bars Theatre Comedy What's On Opinion Lifestyle Showbiz Fashion Food & Drink Welsh Homes Nostalgia Lifestyle Opinion In Your Area Anglesey Blaenau Gwent Bridgend Caerphilly Carmarthenshire Ceredigion Conwy Denbighshire Flintshire Gwynedd Merthyr Tydfil Monmouthshire Neath Port Talbot Newport Pembrokeshire Powys Rhondda Cynon Valley Pontypridd Torfaen Vale of Glamorgan Wrexham View All Locations Useful Links Contact Us About Us Subscriptions Download our e-editions Letters To The Editor Advertise with us Corrections & Clarifications Reader Panel Terms & Conditions Privacy Policy Cookie Policy RSS Feeds Buy, Sell & Tell Jobs Motors Property Business Directory Family Notices Travel Dating Book an Ad BuySell"]},
{
"id":"sha1:4GGJJ4NFCISDCCWQOGGDRTWSZX3RHBCM//dmvIlnsBjFbX41alAVSLA==",
"source_file":"BL-20130723050052741-00000-4204~opera~8443.warc.gz",
"source_file_offset":569101820,
"url":"http://www.walesonline.co.uk/whats-on/film-tv/movie-review-act-killing-15-5073317",
"url_type":["normal"],
"record_type":"response",
"resourcename":["movie-review-act-killing-15-5073317"],
"host":"walesonline.co.uk",
"domain":"walesonline.co.uk",
"public_suffix":"co.uk",
"content_type_served":"text/html;charset=UTF-8",
"server":["Apache-Coyote/1.1"],
"content_length":143315,
"hash":["sha1:4GGJJ4NFCISDCCWQOGGDRTWSZX3RHBCM"],
"crawl_date":"2013-07-23T15:20:38Z",
"crawl_year":"2013",
"wayback_date":"20130723152038",
"wct_subjects":["Arts & Humanities",
"Society & Culture",
"News and Contemporary Events",
"Sports and Recreation",
"Communities"],
"collection":["100 Best Sites"],
"collections":["100 Best Sites",
"News Sites",
"News Sites|Web only news sites"],
"access_terms":["RRO"],
"content_text_length":14878,
"content_type":["text/html"],
"title":"Movie Review: The Act of Killing (15) - Graham Young - Wales Online",
"content_encoding":"UTF-8",
"content_ffb":"3c21646f",
"content_type_droid":"text/html; version=5",
"links_domains":["bookanad.com",
"newmarket.travel",
"facebook.com",
"pcc.org.uk",
"muzu.tv",
"icnetwork.co.uk",
"mediawales.co.uk",
"twitter.com",
"jobswales.co.uk",
"walesonline.co.uk"],
"links_public_suffixes":["org.uk",
"com",
"tv",
"co.uk",
"travel"],
"elements_used":["dt",
"body",
"link",
"div",
"img",
"noscript",
"figcaption",
"br",
"meta",
"dd",
"time",
"title",
"figure",
"link/@rel=stylesheet",
"style",
"link/@rel=pingback",
"h5",
"dl",
"h4",
"ol",
"h1",
"head",
"h3",
"h2",
"ul",
"form",
"a",
"blockquote",
"label",
"script",
"header",
"footer",
"scr'+'ipt",
"li",
"link/@rel=canonical",
"link/@rel=alternate",
"input",
"iframe",
"p",
"nav",
"html",
"link/@rel=dns-prefetch",
"span"],
"content_type_tika":"text/html; charset=UTF-8",
"content_type_version":"5",
"content_type_full":"text/html; charset=UTF-8; version=5",
"content_type_norm":"html",
"content_language":"en",
"ssdeep_hash_bs_384":"r9NNjWPYF3EZNkds9t44mAhJMgwNoNx+l5FLAerFnG",
"ssdeep_hash_bs_768":"r9NNKPYF0lmsmgwizYA2FnG",
"ssdeep_hash_ngram_bs_384":"r9NNjWPYF3EZNkds9t44mAhJMgwNoNx+l5FLAerFnG",
"ssdeep_hash_ngram_bs_768":"r9NNKPYF0lmsmgwizYA2FnG",
"crawl_dates":["2013-07-23T15:20:38Z"],
"crawl_years":["2013"],
"_version_":1569733276986245121,
"type":"Other",
"content":["Jobs Motors Property Business Directory Family Notices Travel Dating Book an Ad BuySell Subscriptions Contact Us How we use Cookies Your Account Edit Profile Logout Wales Online 5 day forecast » Home News Latest News Wales News Business UK News World News Crime Politics Health Education Farming News Opinion Trending Today Kate Middleton Prince Charles, Prince of Wales The Queen Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh Richard Burton Popular this week Letters to the Editor British and Irish Lions Politics Warren Gatland Sam Warburton Top News Live: Wales breaking news, Tuesday 23 July, 2013 live The latest live news, sport, traffic, weather and comment from Wales Royal baby news: Wait continues for first glimpse of Kate Middleton and Prince William's new baby Population of Wales' cities to rocket as number of people living in poorer areas shrinks News Opinion Sion Barry on the future for Cardiff Airport The Welsh Government has its own plans for the long-term development of Cardiff\" David Williamson on electioneering For Conservatives to have any hope of winning in target ares such as Delyn, Derby and Dudley they must acknowledge what a torrid half-decade it has been for many families\" Sport Latest Sport Rugby Football Cardiff City Swansea City Boxing Cricket Ice Hockey Other Sport Sport Opinion Trending Today Vincent Tan Sam Hammam Steve Borley Brendan Rodgers Huw Jenkins Popular this week British and Irish Lions Wales Rugby Team Cardiff City FC Swansea City FC Sam Warburton Top Sport Swansea City tie up £12m signing of Ivory Coast star Wilfried Bony after completing work permit Former Vitesse Arnhem striker Wilfried Bony is now officially a Swan after completing his complicated work permit Cardiff City targetting Toulouse midfielder Etienne Capoue, according to reports Racing Metro deny move for Lions and Wales star Leigh Halfpenny Sport Opinion Terry Phillips on Cardiff City's pre-season training tour in Switzerland Bellamy was a front-runner and Kevin McNaughton impressed time and again\" Chris Wathan on Jonathan De Guzman's place in Swansea City's team What is not straightforward is just who is in Laudrup’s mind when it comes to his midfield three\" What's On Latest What's On Find Things To Do Film & TV Music Restaurants & Bars Theatre Comedy What's On Opinion Trending Today Bruce Springsteen Richard Burton Helena Bonham Carter Katherine Jenkins Dylan Thomas Popular this week Restaurant reviews Katherine Jenkins Catherine Zeta-Jones Tom Jones Book reviews Top What's On Bruce Springsteen Cardiff: Fans swarm the city streets updated Bruce Springsteen fans have swarmed to Cardiff in their thousands today to enjoy one of the last great rockstars in the summer sunshine Review: Burton And Taylor on BBC Four updated Fans queue for two days to secure spot at the front for Bruce Springsteen's Cardiff concert What's On Opinion Peter Collins on the Capital City Jazz Orchestra It was an entertaining evening of music-making with the band playing a selection of classics and more unusual numbers\" Alison Stokes on 9 To 5 The Musical Like Parton herself, 9 To 5 The Musical is unpretentious, unashamed fun\" Lifestyle Latest Lifestyle Showbiz Fashion Food & Drink Welsh Homes Nostalgia Lifestyle Opinion Trending Today Bruce Springsteen Kate Middleton Richard Burton Anthony Hopkins Catherine Zeta-Jones Popular this week Welsh history Hay Festival Wales Book of the Year Beauty Book reviews Top Lifestyle Gabby Logan: BBC boss scolded me over 'too glamorous' boots TV presenter Gabby, 40,  has defended her glossy on-screen appearance after revealing she was told off for her high-heeled footwear live Live: A day in the life of Hannah Jones, supplements & Week End magazine editor updated Royal Welsh Show: Hopes for record crowds at Llanelwedd if weather holds Lifestyle Opinion Peter Collins on The Ashes Strangely, it was not much fun watching our boys thrashing the lads from Down Under at the Home of Cricket. One would have wished for more of a competition.\" Graham Henry on Royal Baby I can objectively say that Royal fever has reached a point that borders on alarming\" In Your Area North Wales Mid Wales South-East Wales South-West Wales Cardiff Swansea Anglesey Blaenau Gwent Bridgend Caerphilly Carmarthenshire Ceredigion Conwy Cynon Valley Denbighshire Flintshire Gwynedd Merthyr Tydfil Monmouthshire Neath Port Talbot Newport Pembrokeshire Powys Rhondda Pontypridd Torfaen Vale of Glamorgan Wrexham Buy, Sell & Tell Jobs Jobs Search for jobs in Wales Motors Motors Find new & used cars for sale Property Property Buying, Selling or Renting? Business Directory Business Directory Search our local business directory Family Notices Family Notices View latest announcements online Travel Travel Find and book your next holiday with us Dating Dating Looking for a date in Wales? Book an Ad Book an Ad Create Private and Trade ads BuySell BuySell Buy or sell 1000s of new and used items Search: Please provide search keyword(s) Hot Topic: Royal Welsh Show - Wales Book of the Year - Katherine Jenkins - Catherine Zeta-Jones Follow Us: Facebook Facebook WalesOnline The latest Wales news, sport, weather and events from Wales Online Wales Rugby News The home of all the latest news from the Welsh rugby scene. Cardiff City News All your Cardiff City news from the Wales Online sports desk. Swansea City News All your Swansea City news from the Wales Online sports desk. Twitter Follow us on Twitter @walesonline The latest Wales news, sport, weather and events from Wales Online @walesrugby Latest Welsh Rugby News from WalesOnline - Western Mail, South Wales Echo and Wales on Sunday @welsh_football All your Welsh football news from the Wales Online sports desk @yourcardiff The latest Cardiff news, business, crime and transport from WalesOnline Newsletters Subscribe Daily bulletin A daily bulletin of the best news and sport from WalesOnline Home What's On Film & TV Comments By Graham Young Movie Review: The Act of Killing (15) 12 Jul 2013 10:08 Graham Young is enthralled by this truly remarkable, real-life alternative to movies like Downfall and The Last King of Scotland The Act of Killing (15) Graham Young ***** The Act of Killing If this was Big Brother: The Movie, it would be interesting to see how many negative headlines it would get with regard its scenes of torture, brutality and murder. But this isn’t just any old TV reality show turned into a film, but a documentary about the sometimes hideous nature of reality. Director Joshua Oppenheimer set out to document the million-plus ‘communist’ victims of gangsters in the Indonesia of 1965 – and ended up putting some of the surviving perpetrators into the spotlight instead. By giving them a gleefully-accepted chance to reenact their brutality, appearing like film stars in their own high-camp versions of the American thrillers that used to make them money, The Act of Killing exposes the killers’ real personalities and questions Hollywood’s portrayal of violence, too. “We killed as fast as possible because we didn’t want a big crowd,” says one. “Americans killed the Indians. Has anyone been punished for that?” asks another. Being overlong at 122 minutes and the fact that the subjects are not well known ‘hate’ figures like Col Gaddafi, Saddam Hussein or Robert Mugabe is immaterial. As insights into the darkest corners of human mentality go, this is a truly remarkable, real-life alternative to movies like Downfall (the last days of Hitler) and The Last King of Scotland (the Idi Amin story). After 1,000 killings can there be any remorse lurking inside a Frog Squad leader like Anwar Congo (initially described as ‘executioner, 1965’ but later comparing himself to Sidney Poitier). “Honestly, I never thought it would look this awful,” he says of the real terror he feels playing a victim in his own film.     Best of Wales Music Videos on MUZU.TV. See more stories you'll love You've turned off story recommendations. Turn them on and we'll update the list below with stories we think you'll love (how we do this). Recommended in What's On Why? Millennium Stadium Bruce Springsteen Cardiff: Fans swarm the city streets Bruce Springsteen Fans queue for two days to secure spot at the front for Bruce Springsteen's Cardiff concert Film & TV What's on TV tonight: Rachel Bruno: My Dad and Me, Kirstie’s Fill Your House For Free and Holby City Millennium Stadium Bruce Springsteen Cardiff preview: The Boss brings his epic show to Cardiff Festival Number Six Manic Street Preachers unveil new single Show Me The Wonder Bruce Springsteen Bruce Springsteen: Millennium Stadium queues already forming as fans seek front-row spots to watch The Boss Katherine Jenkins Katherine Jenkins' Twitter account hacked by Selena Gomez fan What's On   Find something to do tonight in your area Most Read in What's On Millennium Stadium Bruce Springsteen Cardiff preview: The Boss brings his epic show to Cardiff Bruce Springsteen Fans queue for two days to secure spot at the front for Bruce Springsteen's Cardiff concert Millennium Stadium Bruce Springsteen Cardiff: Fans swarm the city streets Bruce Springsteen Bruce Springsteen: Millennium Stadium queues already forming as fans seek front-row spots to watch The Boss Essential Wales Bruce Springsteen, Cardiff: What time is Bruce Springsteen on stage at the Cardiff Millennium Stadium? Travel advice, parking tips and more Cardiff 10k   Info and updates on the 2013 Cardiff 10k and Fun Run See more stories you'll love You've turned off story recommendations. Turn them on and we'll update the list below with stories we think you'll love (how we do this). Recommended Why? Swansea City FC Swansea City set to revive interest in Manchester City frontman John Guidetti, according to reports News Live: Wales breaking news, Tuesday 23 July, 2013 Cardiff Population of Wales' cities to rocket as number of people living in poorer areas shrinks Football News Swansea City tie up £12m signing of Ivory Coast star Wilfried Bony after completing work permit In The News Work to start on tribute park to tragic Welsh boy Harry Lifestyle Live: A day in the life of Hannah Jones, Supplements & Week End magazine editor Millennium Stadium Bruce Springsteen Cardiff: Fans swarm the city streets Crime Man arrested after 17-hour overnight siege at his Cardiff house Andre Villas Boas Manchester United have to act fast to land Gareth Bale as Read Madrid close in, say reports Cardiff Airport Cardiff Airport must move back into profit before considering selling any equity stake Outdoor adventures for kids: the must-read list   Check out great days out for children in Wales Find a local business   Search for local businesses in your area Nostalgia   Check out brilliant pictures from our archives Follow Us Contact Us Send A Story Advertise The Editor Journalists Join us on social media. For the latest local news straight to your Twitter, Facebook feed, e-mail inbox or tablet. Twitter @walesonline @walesrugby @welsh_football @yourcardiff Facebook WalesOnline Welsh Rugby News Cardiff City Swansea City E-Editions Download our e-editions here. Contact us Got a story in your area? Is there something happening in your area you would like us to report on? Email newsdesk@walesonline.co.uk Phone 029 2024 3630 Postal Address WalesOnline, Media Wales, Six Park Street, Cardiff, CF10 1XR Contacts Newsdesk 029 2024 3630 newsdesk@walesonline.co.uk Head of Web: Paul Rowland 029 2024 3626 paul.rowland@walesonline.co.uk Picturedesk 029 2024 3649 rob.norman@walesonline.co.uk Photosales: Saffron Herbert 029 2024 4330 saffron.herbert@walesonline.co.uk Competitions and promotions: Victoria Gladwin 029 2024 4314 victoria.gladwin@walesonline.co.uk Work experience queries steffan.rhys@walesonline.co.uk Organised a special event? Tell us about it and, if possible, send us a picture Contact Pat English Phone 029 2024 3680 Email pat.english@walesonline.co.uk Complaints WalesOnline.co.uk conforms to the newspaper industry's voluntary Code of Practice, administered by the Press Complaints Commission. If you feel we have made an error in a report, or have fallen below our usual high standards, please write in the first instance to: Ceri Gould, Online Editor, WalesOnline.co.uk, Media Wales, Six Park Street, Cardiff CF10 1XR. Tel: 029 2024 3672. Email: ceri.gould@mediawales.co.uk The PCC code of practice, along with details of how to complain, is available from Halton House, 20/23 High Holborn, London EC1N 2JD. Website www.pcc.org.uk or email complaints@pcc.org.uk telephone 020 7831 0022, helpline 0845 600 2757. Send a story Email newsdesk@walesonline.co.uk Phone 029 2024 2630 Postal Address Newsdesk, Media Wales, Six Park Street, Cardiff CF10 1XR Advertise with WalesOnline We reach over 1,384,563* unique users a month with dedicated coverage of all things Welsh. To book an advert with WalesOnline call 029 2024 4296, email pedr.roberts@walesonline.co.uk or visit Media Wales website for more information WalesOnline is part of Media Wales, publisher of the Western Mail, South Wales Echo, Wales on Sunday and the seven Celtic weekly titles, offering you unique access to our audience across Wales online and in print. The Editor Ceri Gould Editor, WalesOnline Email ceri.gould@walesonline.co.uk Ceri has been editor of WalesOnline since April 2012. She was previously executive editor of Media Wales and deputy editor of the Western Mail. She started her career on the Glamorgan Gazette. Journalists David Williamson Political Editor Martin Shipton Chief Reporter Peter Law Chief Reporter Clare Hutchinson Crime Correspondent Gareth Evans Education Correspondent Julia McWatt Health Editor Karen Price Arts Editor Sion Barry Business Editor Paul Abbandonato Head of Sport Chris Wathan Swansea City Correspondent Terry Phillips Cardiff City Correspondent Simon Thomas Rugby Correspondent Andy Howell Rugby Correspondent News Wales News Business UK News World News Crime Health Politics Education Farming News Opinion Sport Rugby Football Cardiff City Swansea City Boxing Ice Hockey Cricket Rugby League Tennis Golf Cycling Athletics Sport Opinion What's On Find Things To Do Film & TV Music Restaurants & Bars Theatre Comedy What's On Opinion Lifestyle Showbiz Fashion Food & Drink Welsh Homes Nostalgia Lifestyle Opinion In Your Area Anglesey Blaenau Gwent Bridgend Caerphilly Carmarthenshire Ceredigion Conwy Denbighshire Flintshire Gwynedd Merthyr Tydfil Monmouthshire Neath Port Talbot Newport Pembrokeshire Powys Rhondda Cynon Valley Pontypridd Torfaen Vale of Glamorgan Wrexham View All Locations Useful Links Contact Us About Us Subscriptions Download our e-editions Letters To The Editor Advertise with us Corrections & Clarifications Reader Panel Terms & Conditions Privacy Policy Cookie Policy RSS Feeds Buy, Sell & Tell Jobs Motors Property Business Directory Family Notices Travel Dating Book an Ad BuySell"]},
{
"id":"sha1:BMZOT3WFWB3RFKYUMQ4TPAPWWP3X4WHT/fK92X/EcnTPBkDsOdEvqqw==",
"source_file":"BL-20131002184248830-00008-25739~opera~8443.warc.gz",
"source_file_offset":534027411,
"url":"http://www.eastsussex.gov.uk/NR/rdonlyres/557CA18B-6219-4787-B4A4-C83184D3DEF8/31231/MinsSMED12June2012.pdf",
"url_type":["normal"],
"record_type":"response",
"resourcename":["MinsSMED12June2012.pdf"],
"content_type_ext":"pdf",
"host":"eastsussex.gov.uk",
"domain":"eastsussex.gov.uk",
"public_suffix":"gov.uk",
"content_type_served":"application/pdf",
"server":["Microsoft-IIS/6.0"],
"content_length":12275,
"hash":["sha1:BMZOT3WFWB3RFKYUMQ4TPAPWWP3X4WHT"],
"crawl_date":"2013-10-03T03:51:15Z",
"crawl_year":"2013",
"wayback_date":"20131003035115",
"access_terms":["OA"],
"content":["STRATEGIC MANAGEMENT AND ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT DECISIONS made by the Lead Cabinet Member for Strategic Management and Economic Development, Councillor Jones on 12 June 2012 at County Hall, Lewes Councillor Glazier spoke on item 4 (see minute 3) Councillor Stogdon spoke on item 5 (see minute 4) 1. MINUTES 1.1 Councillor Jones approved as a correct record the minutes of the meeting held on 24 June 2011. 2. REPORT 2.1 Copies of the reports referred to below are contained in the minute book. 3. PROPOSED ROMNEY MARSH NUCLEAR RESEARCH AND DISPOSAL FACILITY 3.1 Councillor Jones considered a report by the Director of Economy, Transport and Environment concerning proposals for a Romney Marsh Nuclear Research and Disposal Facility and seeking his views as to whether the proposals should be supported. DECISION 3.2 RESOLVED – That, in the absence of sufficient information on geological suitability, safety, infrastructure requirements, environmental protection, economic benefit and community support, it is considered that there is insufficient evidence to support proposals for a Romney Marsh Nuclear Research and Disposal Facility. Reasons 3.3 At this stage there are many unknowns, including geology, economic benefit, infrastructure requirements and community support. Therefore, support for a Nuclear Research and Disposal Facility on the East Sussex borders should only be considered against evidence that demonstrates viability, economic benefit, safety, environmental protection and the community both next to and adjacent to a proposed Facility is in support. 4. THE BRUCE-LOCKHART MEMBER SCHOLARSHIP 4.1 Councillor Jones considered a report by the Chief Executive which sought Lead Member endorsement for the County Council’s support and part-funding of the Bruce- Lockhart Member Scholarship with a review after two years. DECISION 4.2 RESOLVED – To endorse the County Council’s support and part-funding of the Bruce-Lockhart Member Scholarship with a review after two years. Reasons 4.3 East Sussex County Council is committed to the training and development of elected Members and the Lead Member for Strategic Management and Economic Development has approved the support and part-funding of the Bruce-Lockhart Member Scholarship bursary. As this is the first year of the scholarship, East Sussex County Council’s commitment to the Bruce-Lockhart Member Scholarship is being approved for two years, allowing for a review of the success of the initiative. STRATEGIC MANAGEMENT AND ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT"],
"content_text_length":2514,
"content_type":["application/pdf"],
"title":"Meeting of the Lead Member for Strategic Management and Economic Development - Individual Decision Making Meeting held at 2.00 pm at County Hall, St Annes Crescent, Lewes, East Sussex",
"description":["Minutes"],
"author":"Lead Member for Strategic Management and Economic Development - Individual Decision Making Meeting",
"last_modified_year":"2012",
"last_modified":"2012-06-12T15:54:33Z",
"generator":["Acrobat PDFMaker 10.1 for Word",
"Acrobat Distiller 10.1.2 (Windows)"],
"content_ffb":"25504446",
"content_type_droid":"application/pdf; version=1.5",
"content_type_tika":"application/pdf",
"content_type_version":"1.5",
"content_type_full":"application/pdf; version=1.5",
"content_type_norm":"pdf",
"content_language":"en",
"ssdeep_hash_bs_48":"AczPiMACa0+MQgGJ08qpMM9FoWGaG3fZoqtrzX",
"ssdeep_hash_bs_96":"AWZ+M/F8tM9mWGaG3fZoqVX",
"ssdeep_hash_ngram_bs_48":"AczPiMACa0+MQgGJ08qpMM9FoWGaG3fZoqtrzX",
"ssdeep_hash_ngram_bs_96":"AWZ+M/F8tM9mWGaG3fZoqVX",
"crawl_dates":["2013-10-03T03:51:15Z"],
"crawl_years":["2013"],
"_version_":1569733107856179200,
"type":"Other"},
{
"id":"sha1:D35FQJOAFXBCZ7QPLBXK2GA3BMHNTY5Q/WM4OYCYCMRVPim2Uw5xOfA==",
"source_file":"BL-20130723050052741-00000-4204~opera~8443.warc.gz",
"source_file_offset":647978874,
"url":"http://www.guardian.co.uk/profile/bruceackerman",
"url_type":["normal"],
"record_type":"response",
"resourcename":["bruceackerman"],
"host":"guardian.co.uk",
"domain":"guardian.co.uk",
"public_suffix":"co.uk",
"server":["Apache"],
"content_type_served":"text/html; charset=utf-8",
"content_length":102422,
"hash":["sha1:D35FQJOAFXBCZ7QPLBXK2GA3BMHNTY5Q"],
"crawl_date":"2013-07-23T19:55:25Z",
"crawl_year":"2013",
"wayback_date":"20130723195525",
"access_terms":["RRO"],
"content_text_length":6130,
"content_type":["text/html"],
"title":"Bruce Ackerman | The Guardian",
"keywords":["Global"],
"content_encoding":"UTF-8",
"content_ffb":"20202020",
"content_type_droid":"text/html; version=5",
"links_domains":["e-printphoto.co.uk",
"guardian.co.uk",
"guardianbookshop.co.uk",
"newspaperdirect.com"],
"links_public_suffixes":["com",
"co.uk"],
"elements_used":["body",
"sc\"",
"link/@rel=shortcut icon",
"link",
"div",
"img",
"noscript",
"meta",
"title",
"link/@rel=stylesheet",
"style",
"button",
"link/@rel=publisher",
"e.length;b++){c=e[b].substr(0,e[b].indexof(\"=\"));d=e[b].substr(e[b].indexof(\"=\")+1);c=c.replace(",
"h4",
"ol",
"head",
"h1",
"option",
"h3",
"h2",
"ul",
"form",
"select",
"a",
"link/@rel=shorturl",
"script",
"li",
"link/@rel=alternate",
"link/@rel=canonical",
"input",
"strong",
"p",
"scr\"",
"html",
"scr'",
"span"],
"content_type_tika":"text/html; charset=UTF-8",
"content_type_version":"5",
"content_type_full":"text/html; charset=UTF-8; version=5",
"content_type_norm":"html",
"content_language":"en",
"ssdeep_hash_bs_96":"kpujz5m8nWBC9nNWiyQ+0jLAD6ozV6/6GXkzWqDmZ3EnmYHrMxmMK5GDL7jdCzM/",
"ssdeep_hash_bs_192":"kYz5qYcMANp6/6GWmGfLMUccMLf1em",
"ssdeep_hash_ngram_bs_96":"kpujz5m8nWBC9nNWiyQ+0jLAD6ozV6/6GXkzWqDmZ3EnmYHrMxmMK5GDL7jdCzM/",
"ssdeep_hash_ngram_bs_192":"kYz5qYcMANp6/6GWmGfLMUccMLf1em",
"crawl_dates":["2013-07-23T19:55:25Z"],
"crawl_years":["2013"],
"_version_":1569737428063748096,
"type":"Other",
"content":["Turn autoplay off Turn autoplay on Please activate cookies in order to turn autoplay off Jump to content [s] Jump to site navigation [0] Jump to search [4] Terms and conditions [8] Edition: UK US AU Your activity Email subscriptions Account details Linked services Profile Mobile About us About us, Contact us Press office Guardian Print Centre Guardian readers' editor Observer readers' editor Terms of service Privacy policy Advertising guide Digital archive Digital edition Guardian Weekly Buy Guardian and Observer photos Today's paper The Guardian G2 features Comment and debate Editorials, letters and corrections Obituaries Other lives Sport EducationGuardian Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe to the Guardian iPhone app iPad edition Kindle Extra Guardian Weekly Digital edition The Guardian User comments News Sport Comment Culture Business Money Life & style Travel Environment Tech TV Video Dating Offers Jobs Global Bruce Ackerman RSS Profile Bruce Ackerman is Sterling professor of law and political science at Yale, and the author of Before the Next Attack: Preserving Civil Liberties in an Age of Terrorism (2006) and, most recently, The Decline and Fall of the American Republic (2010) Latest How to make a European constitution for the 21st century 3 Oct 2012: Bruce Ackerman and Miguel Maduro: Europe needs a solution to its crisis that will be accepted by its citizens. The South African model may be the answer How to resolve the War Powers impasse 3 Jun 2011: Bruce Ackerman and Oona Hathaway: Dennis Kucinich is wrong about Libya but right about the law: Congress and the president must fix this War Powers Act hiatus Bradley Manning's inhumane treatment 11 Apr 2011: Bruce Ackerman and others: Open letter: The president's own legal training must tell him how the abuse of the alleged WikiLeaks source violates constitutional norms Did Congress approve America's longest war? 27 Jan 2011: Bruce Ackerman and Oona Hathaway: Congress did empower the president in 2001 to pursue al-Qaida in Afghanistan. But a decade later, where's the oversight? Charging Julian Assange could be unconstitutional 10 Dec 2010: Bruce Ackerman and Sara Aronchick Solow: The due process clause rules out prosecuting WikiLeaks' founder – a non-US citizen – for extraterritorial offences Laugh Lines: from Sergeant Bilko to Father Ted 13 May 2010: Bruce Dessau's guide to TV comedy: Forget Steve Martin, it is the spirit of Phil Silvers that is resurrected on Craggy Island Why the Lib Dems do well out of TV debates 29 Apr 2010: Bruce Ackerman and James Fishkin: The leaders' debates have prompted voters to re-examine their old party identities in light of their policy preferences A national endowment for journalism 13 Feb 2009: Bruce Ackerman and Ian Ayres: Efforts to save print newspapers are missing the point. The real question is how to save investigative reporting A legal time bomb in Iraq 12 Dec 2008: Bruce Ackerman and Oona Hathaway: Obama must return US foreign policy to the rule of law - and the mandate for war is about to expire The coming transatlantic crisis 2 Sep 2008: Bruce Ackerman: Russia's resurgence as a world power and America's decline mean that US and European interests are on a collision course What Georgia means for Europe 12 Aug 2008: Bruce Ackerman: Russia's military hostilities in Georgia provides a new impetus for strengthening the European Union Where money is no object 26 Jan 2008: Bruce Ackerman and Ian Ayres: Peter Hain's disgrace will inevitably lead to calls for campaign finance reform. The best solution is for political donations to be made anonymously into blind trusts Checks, please 15 Jan 2008: Bruce Ackerman: US elections 2008: The US political system succeeds, not fails, when it stalls large change until there is a broad consensus to support it Inherit the windfall 11 Oct 2007: Bruce Ackerman and Anne Alstott: Funding baby bonds with the tax on private inheritance is both fair and just. What we owe 'suspected terrorists' 23 Jul 2007: Bruce Ackerman: Compensating detainees who turn out to be innocent is the right thing to do, and would create economic incentives that improve the fight against terrorism. Next 1 2 1-15 of 17 for Bruce Ackerman Today's best video The week in TV Telly addict Andrew Collins reviews Britain's Favourite Supermarket Foods, Run, Family Tree (starring Chris O'Dowd, above) and Ray Donovan Chris Froome wins the Tour de France 2013 Take a look back at some of Chris Froome's finest moments in the 100th Tour de France Royal birth announced outside Buckingham Palace Baby prince confirmed on notice on easel at royal residence Best summer plug plants Alys Fowler on the best plants for your space and shrubs with varied seasons of interest On The Guardian Most viewed Latest Last 24 hours 1.  UK news: Royal baby: Duchess of Cambridge leaves hospital with new prince – live 2. Society: Jack Monroe: the face of modern poverty 3. UK news: Royal baby jokes: how Twitter reacted 4. Football: Football quiz: Panini stickers 5. UK news: Man charged with murder of PC Keith Blakelock at Broadwater Farm riots More most viewed Last 24 hours 1.  Yemeni journalist who reported US drone strike is released from jail 2. Pope Francis greeted by ecstatic crowds in Brazil - video 3. Summer storms and Royal baby latest: the best news photographs of the day 4. Royal baby: Duchess of Cambridge leaves hospital with new prince – live 5. How Taliban brought new terror to Pakistan's Killer Mountain All today's stories This week's bestsellers 1.  Holloway by Robert Macfarlane £10.99 2.  Reason I Jump: One Boy's Voice from the Silence of Autism by Naoki Higashida £10.39 3.  Sweet Tooth by Ian McEwan £4.79 4.  Racing Hard by William Fotheringham £8.99 5.  Sleepwalkers by Christopher Clark £8.49 Search the Guardian bookshop Search Sponsored feature License/buy our content | Privacy policy | Terms & conditions | Advertising guide | Accessibility | A-Z index | Inside the Guardian blog | About us | Work for us | Join our dating site today © 2013 Guardian News and Media Limited or its affiliated companies. All rights reserved. Close notifications (beta)"]}]
}}